<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support Driven Jobs</title>
    <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jobs.supportdriven.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description>Support Driven Jobs</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 11:18:37 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 11:18:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>EventMobi Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/eventmobi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 8 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/eventmobi.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EventMobi is changing the way event planners create, market and manage their events, as well as how attendees experience events using their smartphones and tablets for thousands of events, conferences and tradeshows around the world. Clients like Motorola, Ralph Lauren, Nestle, Intel and Canadian Heart &amp;amp;amp; Stroke Foundation have used EventMobi to enhance the attendee experience at their events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Want to quickly figure out what EventMobi is all about? Then watch this fun 3min video here: &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.eventmobi.com/careers/#video&amp;quot;&amp;gt;http://www.eventmobi.com/careers/#video&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wondering how our technology is affecting the world and the meeting industry in general? Well here is an awesome infographic that summarizes what we have achieved this past and why we are super excited for 2016: &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.eventmobi.com/about/company/2015/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;http://www.eventmobi.com/about/company/2015/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What impact will you have?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;First point of contact for our amazing clients when they need help - Our clients are generally professional event planners working at associations or large corporations. -The end user of our product however are attendees around the world from all ages and professions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Lead client onboarding process from end-to-end&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Handle inquiries about app development and troubleshoot client needs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take accountability to solve issues from beginning to end.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Liaise with Engineering team to help drive feature development for our product&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Receive and incorporate client feedback to improve business performance&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proactively profile customer needs and match our products and services to those needs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;This is a chance to learn and be involved at every point of the company while helping and building relationships with a wide range of EventMobi clients across the world.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;10% travel is required: our clients often need our support team to help in the execution of their event&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Limited evening and weekend work may be required to help with peak times based on client needs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What will you bring to the team?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;An empathetic desire to help: For you, a new inquiry isn’t a just case to close, but an opportunity to understand someone’s story and make their life better. Our purpose as a company is to help event planners thrive.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Superb communication skills: You understand that effective communication is about more than what you say, it’s about taking the time to listen and understand. You can make complicated concepts sound easy or describe in detail the simplest of interactions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A deep understanding of software and the web: You won’t need to know how to code, but terms like HTML and CSS shouldn’t be foreign to you. You can quickly learn complex procedures, troubleshoot potential bugs on the fly (pun intended), and visualize customers’ screens from their description alone.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer facing experience: Whether it was building a rapport with customers at Starbucks/Apple, or working in a customer-centric call centre, you must have experience working with customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong interpersonal skills - ability to work with people with a variety of skill sets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can you make good choices that serve both the customer and company? We need folks who are passionate about delighting and retaining customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Aircall Customer Support Hero</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/aircall.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/aircall.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;ll join the US business team to ensure that the customers we work with have a great experience. You will be the first point of contact and advocate for clients.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What are the responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be the voice of Aircall - you will be on the front lines! This involves flexing your amazing troubleshooting skills via phone calls, emails, and live chat.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide swift and thorough solutions for customers. When absolutely unable to do so, escalate to the dev/tech team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take note and relay customer feedback and insights to Aircall&amp;#39;s internal teams such as the tech, marketing and product teams, in order to constantly improve the customer experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Maintain an expert-level knowledge of our products and internal management systems as well as curiosity and awareness of new initiatives within in the industry.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What we are looking for:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have at least 1+ year of experience in Support and are passionate about it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are technical and problem solver. UDP/TCP ports, REST API and packet losses do mean something to you.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have a “no task is too small” attitude and the endurance to consistently deliver amazing customer experiences without exception.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have superior written and oral communication skills.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have strong people skills — you are friendly, a good listener, you ask good questions, and you&amp;#39;re energized by personal interaction.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are a team player who works well with a wide range of personalities and is ready to contribute to an awesome team environment.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Brownie points:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have a sense of humour and know how to make fun of yourself.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flexibility with schedule to meet the needs of the business.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What are the benefits of working here?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;All the caffeine you need to keep you going&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Medical/Vision/Dental benefits&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tax-free commuter benefits&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Your metrocard reimbursed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Gym reimbursement&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Shiny new Mac gear!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Automattic Happiness Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/automattic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/automattic.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Happiness Engineer, helping people is your passion. Maybe you’ve developed your own support philosophy by reading books like Delivering Happiness or Exceptional Service, Exceptional Profit. Perhaps you’re a contributor in an online support community such as the &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums or &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Transforming publishing on the web is no small task. Our goal is to build relationships based on trust which result in happy, passionate, loyal customers and colleagues. We do this through listening to their needs and guiding them to the fullest use of the products we offer. We are looking for people with the right mix of compassion, writing skills, and technical knowledge to get the job done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;In general, a typical day involves:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Helping people use Automattic’s products, including &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, WooCommerce, Jetpack, Gravatar, and more&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshooting, investigating, and creating detailed bug reports&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Crafting and editing helpful support documentation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being an active member of a team that provides around the clock support to our users via live chat, forums, and email&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Building a community of support by sharing knowledge and insight amongst team members&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Being a Happiness Engineer requires:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Patience, grace, and a sense of humor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent writing and communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working knowledge of WordPress, HTML, and CSS&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A knack for taking technical language and making it understandable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A passion for solving tough problems and proposing elegant solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happiness Engineers must be fluent and eloquent in written English. If you know additional languages, be sure to tell us!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums are fantastic places to gain the experience required for this position. If you are already active there, let us know! Send a link to your forum profile and we’ll check it out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Account Support Manager Asia Pacific (Remote)</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-account-apac.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-account-apac.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub&amp;#39;s user base is growing and the web support team is growing with it. We&amp;#39;re looking for a web support team manager located in the Europe or Asia Pacific to help lead our passionate, distributed support staff and work with them to create effective and efficient support processes and solve users&amp;#39; problems. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in Europe and Asia Pacific, so legal working authorization is required: Japan, Australia, New Zealand, Austria, Croatia, Denmark, England, France, Germany, Ireland, Netherlands, Scotland, Spain, Sweden, and Switzerland.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Web Support EU-APAC Accounts Manager will work with their team members to provide guidance and support in the day-to-day work environment. The manager will also work side-by-side with the team answering emails and help resolve users&amp;#39; issues as quickly and awesomely as possible. The manager will also participate in the weekly management meetings providing input and guidance into the team direction and future growth of the organization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they email support. We help people as quickly and awesomely as possible. Our Account Support team handles a wide range of questions that require a logical brain and a spidey sense to investigate and determine the appropriate solution to many of the problems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Web Support EU-APAC Accounts Manager will report to the Director of Web Support, who will help maintain open lines of communication among team members and help keep work focused on things that are important to the individuals, the team, and the company. They will also keep communication open with the Engineering and Product teams to serve everyone involved. The Web Support EU-APAC Accounts Manager will work with the Human Resources team to help resolve personnel issues as they arise as well as hiring for Web Support.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Meeting 1-1 with team members on a regular basis&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Planning and supporting career development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Giving guided performance feedback&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Serving as a coach and mentor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Keeping communication channels open within the entire Support team as well as cross-functionally&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Serving as hiring manager for the team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Participating in management conversations about the day-to-day business as well as future direction and stratergy of the team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Responding to user emails&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working with Engineering to resolve problems on GitHub.com&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Driving efficiencies within support tools and processes&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tracking and monitoring project progress and ensuring deliverables are completed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;YOU SHOULD HAVE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must currently reside in one of the following: Japan, Australia, New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must have current working authorization in country listed above&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar written and verbal communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with managing people&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Passionate about creating and fostering good support practices&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to empathize with a diverse range of people&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy and the ability to advocate for others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A malleable writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have worked with a distributed team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;BONUS POINTS FOR:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Managing a remote team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hiring experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer support experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, elaborate boardgames)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Account Support Manager Europe (Remote)</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-account-eu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-account-eu.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub&amp;#39;s user base is growing and the web support team is growing with it. We&amp;#39;re looking for a web support team manager located in the Europe or Asia Pacific to help lead our passionate, distributed support staff and work with them to create effective and efficient support processes and solve users&amp;#39; problems. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in Europe and Asia Pacific, so legal working authorization is required: Japan, Australia, New Zealand, Austria, Croatia, Denmark, England, France, Germany, Ireland, Netherlands, Scotland, Spain, Sweden, and Switzerland.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Web Support EU-APAC Accounts Manager will work with their team members to provide guidance and support in the day-to-day work environment. The manager will also work side-by-side with the team answering emails and help resolve users&amp;#39; issues as quickly and awesomely as possible. The manager will also participate in the weekly management meetings providing input and guidance into the team direction and future growth of the organization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they email support. We help people as quickly and awesomely as possible. Our Account Support team handles a wide range of questions that require a logical brain and a spidey sense to investigate and determine the appropriate solution to many of the problems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Web Support EU-APAC Accounts Manager will report to the Director of Web Support, who will help maintain open lines of communication among team members and help keep work focused on things that are important to the individuals, the team, and the company. They will also keep communication open with the Engineering and Product teams to serve everyone involved. The Web Support EU-APAC Accounts Manager will work with the Human Resources team to help resolve personnel issues as they arise as well as hiring for Web Support.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Meeting 1-1 with team members on a regular basis&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Planning and supporting career development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Giving guided performance feedback&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Serving as a coach and mentor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Keeping communication channels open within the entire Support team as well as cross-functionally&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Serving as hiring manager for the team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Participating in management conversations about the day-to-day business as well as future direction and stratergy of the team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Responding to user emails&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working with Engineering to resolve problems on GitHub.com&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Driving efficiencies within support tools and processes&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tracking and monitoring project progress and ensuring deliverables are completed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;YOU SHOULD HAVE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must currently reside in one of the following: Austria, Croatia, Denmark, England, France, Germany, Ireland, Netherlands, Scotland, Spain, Sweden, and Switzerland.- Must have current working authorization in country listed above&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar written and verbal communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with managing people&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Passionate about creating and fostering good support practices&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to empathize with a diverse range of people&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy and the ability to advocate for others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A malleable writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have worked with a distributed team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;BONUS POINTS FOR:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Managing a remote team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hiring experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer support experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, elaborate boardgames)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Community Manager (North America)</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-community.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-community.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub is looking for a Community Manager to join our Web Support team to create, manage and build awareness for our Community Support Forums. The Community Manager will be responsible for building a strategy that both increases the number of GitHub community users as well as fosters active, productive and helpful discussions within the community. The Community Manager will help shape the product roadmap to serve the community’s needs, and grows and strengthens the GitHub user community.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Community Manager will report to the Director of Web Support and will work closely with our global support, documentation and other cross-organizational teams to ensure consistency throughout the content and voice within the community. The Community Manager will help maintain effective communication between the Community Support team and other teams at GitHub, in order to create the best experience possible for our customers, moderators, and staff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Community Support Forums will be a place for users to collaborate, learn and network with both their peers from the community, as well as GitHub. The Community Manager will be responsible for upholding GitHub’s values within the community, including ensuring participants’ safety, inclusion, and consideration in the forum environment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Residence in North America and have legal working authorization to work in Canada or the US&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;YOU MUST HAVE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proven experience launching community initiatives (e.g. building an online forum, launching programs tailored to specific audiences)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with social media, blogging, and online community engagement&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proven experience developing and implementing strategic plans that grow communities on social media&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Demonstrated ability to work with cross-functional teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience developing community training resources, guidelines, and policies&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;BONUS POINTS IF YOU HAVE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience supporting users at varying skill levels through a number of support channels (chat, CRM systems, blogs, Twitter, etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working directly with engineering teams, creating workflows, and building and integrating systems&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience building metrics to monitor and measure success of community engagement&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of online marketing and marketing channels&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Worked asynchronously with distributed teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Previous experience with GitHub and how developers use the tool&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A positive and enthusiastic attitude and can work effectively in a fast-paced, team environment&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Technical Support</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-tech-apac.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-tech-apac.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Technical Support team is looking for full-time team members in located in North America (US and Canada)! This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub users work 24/7, so you&amp;#39;ll occasionally need to adjust your work week to help cover a weekend or holiday (don&amp;#39;t worry! We strongly support flexible schedules that let you to take care of the important things in your life).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they contact Support and we help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. Technical support handles a wide variety of inquiries including questions about Git and GitHub workflows, GitHub Pages, our API, and our desktop applications. Support also works closely with the engineering team to track down bugs and improve our documentation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;WHAT YOU SHOULD HAVE:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in addition to legal working authorization to work in Japan, Australia, or New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience using GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exposure to programming with a language like Ruby&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Basic experience using Git&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understanding of how websites and web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills – you might not know all the answers but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy – you are attuned to hear the question behind a question&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;BONUS POINTS FOR:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Will love developers and GitHub as much as we do&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Could effortlessly explain how Git works to a non-developer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have remote customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working from the command line&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiar with basic network concepts and tools&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
