<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support Driven Jobs</title>
    <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jobs.supportdriven.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description>Support Driven Jobs</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 15:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 15:42:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Papertrail Customer Success Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/papertrail.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/papertrail.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://papertrailapp.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Papertrail&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; provides log management as a service. We work with tens of thousands of ops-savvy developers, systems engineers, and entrepreneurs at companies like GitHub, Heroku, Instacart, Adobe, and DNSimple.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;#39;s where you come in. We&amp;#39;ve grown to need technical customer support to help customers make the most of Papertrail. Here&amp;#39;s a few examples of what customers think of Papertrail&amp;#39;s support:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://twitter.com/TiuTalk/status/714592766827872257&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/TiuTalk/status/714592766827872257&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://twitter.com/agmakonts/status/730356796607614976&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/agmakonts/status/730356796607614976&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://twitter.com/hectcastro/status/717523363032391680&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/hectcastro/status/717523363032391680&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Summary&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Put smiles on the faces of fellow engineers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Remote work is welcome&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;100% online (email, Slack/Campfire text chat), no phones&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Startup atmosphere and tools, public company benefits&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Okay, cool. What&amp;#39;s involved?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Help customers setup and use Papertrail&amp;#39;s service in email and text chat. The questions are about a wide range of topics like Linux, syslog, Web framework logging, Ruby, Rails, IP stack troubleshooting, PHP, REST/JSON, Python, firewall rules, Node.js, plus non-technical topics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You almost certainly won&amp;#39;t know about all of these. While a strong working knowledge of Linux is required, Googling to satisfy your own curiosity is a lot more valuable (and hopefully, fun). Also:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be comfortable and personable in email, even when interacting with strangers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Show a passion for devops tools, Web services, and technology in general. We&amp;#39;re doing this because we love it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Requirements&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Working Linux knowledge&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. You&amp;#39;ve compiled a binary, installed packages, and understand TCP/IP concepts. Experience with tools like &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;tcpdump&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;strace&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; will help, though it isn&amp;#39;t required.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Fantastic casual writing skills&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. This job involves helping people in email, forums, and text chat, so a written voice goes a long way. Good grammar is critical, as is a gut feel for when to ignore it in order to make a personal connection. When a friend emails you a question, do you spend 10 minutes Googling and send them a ridiculously thoughtful answer? You&amp;#39;ll fit right in. A public online history (like a blog, Stack Overflow/Server Fault posts, GitHub commit history, Twitter account, or casual posts to non-technical online forums) is ideal, since a big part of this job is showing your passion and knowledge for a topic in casual, freeform emails.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Scripting&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Experience in a scripting or programming language, ideally in one or more of Ruby, Python, Go, Java, or C.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Location and timezone&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Able to work in US, Canada, or Europe on a roughly UTC-7 workday. Although we&amp;#39;re completely location-agnostic, employment law is not.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Why is this unusually awesome?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;#39;s the most important thing we do. Happy customers are the only reason why we get to do this every day. Since most of our interactions with customers are via support, this is the most important thing we do every day and the main reason we grow. It&amp;#39;s:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Flexible.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Papertrail&amp;#39;s hub is a Slack text chat channel. Work in a coffee shop without missing office conversation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Personal&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. You&amp;#39;ll be part of a tiny team, working side by side with the founders. Debating product decisions is a lot more fun because we&amp;#39;re all target users – 100% of Papertrail staff has sent a GitHub pull request.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The tip of the iceberg&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Although answering questions is the must-have, you&amp;#39;re welcome to write docs, improve our open-source apps, or grow into coding on the core service. We operate in 3 thriving fields: cloud computing, software as a service, and dev/ops, and the tools we use are in demand: Ruby, Java/Scala, and current open-source libraries.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Predictable&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. As part of SolarWinds, Papertrail offers excellent benefits, including paid health insurance and 401(k) match. If you&amp;#39;re in San Francisco or Austin, you&amp;#39;re welcome to come in to a physical office.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;About Papertrail&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;#39;re part of SolarWinds, which includes &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.librato.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Librato&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.pingdom.com&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Pingdom&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. You can see some of the things we think about on &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://twitter.com/papertrailapp&amp;quot;&amp;gt;@papertrailapp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;SolarWinds (SWI) is on Forbes&amp;#39; lists of &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.forbes.com/growth-companies/list/#tab:rank&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Most Innovative Growth Companies&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.forbes.com/best-small-companies/list/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;America&amp;#39;s Best Small Companies&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>I Will Teach You to be Rich Customer Success Representative</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/iwt.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/iwt.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About Us&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At I Will Teach You to Be Rich, we’re passionate about helping millions of people live richer lives, from starting businesses to finding their dream jobs to even losing weight and becoming more fit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our programs attract thousands of customers worldwide and we strive to deliver top-notch customer support every step of the way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Opportunity&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are looking for an experienced Customer Success Representative who can help us develop our customer support operations to the highest level inside of our dynamic growth phase, as well as create the structures and stability necessary to sustain this growth into the future. Someone who is passionate about customer service and how it can transform businesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As Customer Success Representative, you’ll be accountable for addressing hundreds of customer interactions daily across multiple platforms, including email, live chat and phone. On the front lines of communication with our students, you’ll be instrumental in capturing feedback from our students and channeling it to other teams across the organization to help us deliver the highest quality products and services.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’ll be trained in all our programs and master the frameworks, tools, and techniques we’ve created to change people’s behavior and help them achieve their aspirations. You&amp;#39;ll be immersed in the technologies, systems and processes we use to power our business. This is an opportunity to get in on the ground floor of our rapidly growing company and have a direct impact with our students. Our customer service efforts are evolving and we need people who can evolve with us.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;How You’ll Contribute:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Be an IWT Ambassador&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide superior customer service for customers by demonstrating an in-depth knowledge of the company’s programs, procedures, and policies.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Master the company’s course offerings, effectively identify and recommend best courses for student’s needs.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Respond rapidly and thoroughly to customer inquiries. We strive for an immediate response time during business hours and use an online interface that tracks all communications.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Product Launches&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be an essential part of the success of our monthly product launches. This includes:&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide assistance in preparation of course launches, including proofreading, editing, and testing of products, transactions and community sites.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide pre-sales support to prospective customers in support of course launches, and advise customers on courses that best fit their needs.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Monitor webinars, live chat, email, and phone.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Process Improvement&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;This is a unique opportunity to not only represent IWT on the front-lines, but to also dive in and give insight on how we can improve our processes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Use your creative juices and deep knowledge of our customer base to develop tools such as FAQs, screencast tutorials, help pages, etc, to continually improve the user support experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Assist with evaluating, implementing and maintaining customer service technology and systems, including workflow, help desk, phone systems, chat systems, etc.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Use clear judgment to identify and promptly communicate relevant trends to the Product Development team and technical issues to the IT team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Assist in creating and maintaining training protocols, macros and other processes to keep customer success team continually up-to-date on the company’s products and services.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About You and What You Bring&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience in providing best-in-class communication in a fast-paced, high volume, customer support environment&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2-5 years experience in online customer support role, responding to a high volume of customer inquiries.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You communication style (verbal and written) is clear, concise and reflective of the highest standards of professionalism and customer care.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are exceptionally detail oriented. You believe that it is of utmost important that there are no spelling errors/typos in your communication with our customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have surpassed KPI’s in terms of productivity and performance in previous roles (volume of tickets per week, tickets per hour, and customer satisfaction).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Tech-savvy&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are technically inclined and can pick up new systems and technologies quickly.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have broad knowledge of browsers, MAC and PC platforms, mobile devices, WordPress, and collaboration tools.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have working knowledge of Google Apps, Excel, MS Office products and other leading productivity applications.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Initiative and Flexibility&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are a self-starter / self-motivated, Able to work independently with minimal oversight.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are flexible and can adapt your work schedule to align with peak periods and demands of our business.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Skills you’ll need in order to succeed in this role:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bachelor’s Degree.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2-5 years experience in online customer service or comparable experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior working knowledge of Zendesk or other leading help desk platform.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exceptional written and verbal communication skills with the ability to forge meaningful connections with students using email and chat.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Outstanding attitude - readily accepts change, takes initiative, and responds positively to suggestions and constructive criticism.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience or ability to work remotely (with your own phone, headset, laptop and high speed internet access in place).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Bonus points for:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with IWT products and services and a subscriber to our blog.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working knowledge of InfusionSoft or other popular CRM systems.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Analytics and reporting experience in a customer support function.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Pacific time zone coverage and/or weekend availability.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;This is 100% virtual job - you can work from anywhere (Must be US-based).&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Yeomen Community Support Team Lead</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/yeomen.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/yeomen.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Company:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Yeomen are a community of support experts who build and staff customized support solutions for companies and organizations. We specialize in creating help desks that don’t just resolve problems, but also foster brand loyalty and growth by cultivating relationships with user communities. Our mission is to bring a human element to support by connecting customers to real people who care about customer concerns and work hard to resolve their issues with compassion, care, and positivity. More information about The Yeomen can be found at theyeomen.com.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Yeomen is proud to be a support partner for Vimeo, the leading video platform for creative professionals. We are currently looking for an experienced manager to lead the team of 18 Yeomen support ninjas who engage and support the Vimeo community day in and day out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Job:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a full time position.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Yeomen is based in the United States. This opening is for someone residing within the US that can telecommute from their current location.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What you’d be doing for support:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Answering tech support and customer service questions by email.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshooting video playback issues.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Supporting account access for all level accounts (Basic, Plus, &amp;amp;amp; PRO)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Helping with billing and purchases.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Walking someone through uploading and downloading a video.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Educating users of privacy settings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Identifying recurring customer issues, helping to solve them, and escalating them to others for review.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Writing customer response templates and online help documentation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Making customers very happy.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Having coffee with us.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What you’d be doing for your team:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Liaising between client contact and support team members.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Coordinating schedules, including shift rotations and time off requests for three separate shifts.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Leading monthly one on one meetings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Developing well-rounded metrics for success and using these to help your team grow professionally.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Creating documentation &amp;amp;amp; reporting of performance metrics.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working with members of the team to set and reach career goals.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>AND CO Customer Service Intern</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/and-co.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/and-co.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Is a people-person first and foremost and loves solving problems for others.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Is ready to jump in head first and explore every inch of AND CO to understand how it works so s/he can explain it to others.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Communicates through email and over the phone in a clear, concise and friendly way. Requires as few back-and-forth emails as possible to delight customers, solve their problems and turn them into raving fans (if they aren&amp;#39;t already).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Has deep empathy for customers experiencing problems, and responds appropriately to their emails in a friendly, sympathetic or apologetic manner as the occasion calls for it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Remains bubbly and friendly even when a customer is wrong or acting rude.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Contributes an overall positive energy to the CO team and adds their own enthusiasm and excitement on a day-to-day basis&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BONUS: coffee and cheese are your faves (not in that order or combination).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HOW TO APPLY: Email resume and a brief intro statement to Amanda at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:amanda@and.co&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:&amp;amp;#97;m&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#x6e;&amp;amp;#x64;&amp;amp;#x61;&amp;amp;#x40;&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#x6e;&amp;amp;#x64;.&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#97;m&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#x6e;&amp;amp;#x64;&amp;amp;#x61;&amp;amp;#x40;&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#x6e;&amp;amp;#x64;.&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>PrecisionLender Client Support Superhero</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/precisionlender.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/precisionlender.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Client Support Superhero, you will support, educate, and empower our clients and end-users so that they can be successful. You will own the client support experience and work to exceed clients&amp;#39; expectations by genuinely caring about them, personally &amp;amp;amp; professionally.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What Your Superpowers Are:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Passionately helping others.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Explaining complex issues in beautifully simple terms.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Listening way more than you talk and connecting with people.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Embracing change &amp;amp;amp; adapting quickly.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Managing multiple projects simultaneously.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A natural ability to see the full scope of a problem, in order to ask the right questions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Never letting a detail fall through the cracks.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Using social media or web-based software, including Twitter, Facebook, Google Apps.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with common help-desk/ticketing solutions such as Zendesk and Jira.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;How You Will Use Your Powers:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Saving clients across the country from any issues they are having.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Evaluate, troubleshoot, and follow-up on client issues as well as replicate and document for further escalation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Develop support content including articles, blog posts, videos and other collateral. You may not author all that content, but you will work with our development and consulting teams to identify content needs and get them filled.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being a voice for clients and fighting for their causes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Drive product change and improvement by working with our Product Development team to document changes and improvements to our software and ensure that our Clients are aware of those changes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Foster our community of users to stimulate the sharing of ideas so that we can get our best clients talking to each other and cross-pollinating those ideas.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Your Experience &amp;amp;amp; Education:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You may be fresh out of college or you may have 10 years under your belt - either way, you need to have spent significant time working in a business setting, ideally in areas like customer service, internal and external client support.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;Bachelors Degree preferred&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;How You Should Apply:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;#39;re looking for people who pay attention and care about their future. If you want to be considered for this position, you have to answer the application questions, this is us testing your attention to detail.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The final step in our hiring process will be for you to arrange personal reference calls with former supervisors as well as others we may choose. If you&amp;#39;re awesome, that part will be easy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Automattic Happiness Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/automattic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/automattic.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Happiness Engineer, helping people is your passion. Maybe you’ve developed your own support philosophy by reading books like Delivering Happiness or Exceptional Service, Exceptional Profit. Perhaps you’re a contributor in an online support community such as the &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums or &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Transforming publishing on the web is no small task. Our goal is to build relationships based on trust which result in happy, passionate, loyal customers and colleagues. We do this through listening to their needs and guiding them to the fullest use of the products we offer. We are looking for people with the right mix of compassion, writing skills, and technical knowledge to get the job done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;In general, a typical day involves:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Helping people use Automattic’s products, including &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, WooCommerce, Jetpack, Gravatar, and more&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshooting, investigating, and creating detailed bug reports&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Crafting and editing helpful support documentation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being an active member of a team that provides around the clock support to our users via live chat, forums, and email&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Building a community of support by sharing knowledge and insight amongst team members&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Being a Happiness Engineer requires:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Patience, grace, and a sense of humor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent writing and communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working knowledge of WordPress, HTML, and CSS&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A knack for taking technical language and making it understandable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A passion for solving tough problems and proposing elegant solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happiness Engineers must be fluent and eloquent in written English. If you know additional languages, be sure to tell us!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums are fantastic places to gain the experience required for this position. If you are already active there, let us know! Send a link to your forum profile and we’ll check it out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Harvest Expert</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/harvest.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/harvest.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Disclaimer: Don&amp;#39;t judge us too quickly! We&amp;#39;ve made some intentional typos in this job post. See our To Apply section for more info.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About Harvest&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Harvest creates well-crafted, useful software to help small businesses work better. Today we’re a group of folks &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.getharvest.com/made-on-earth&amp;quot;&amp;gt;all over the globe&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; serving tens of thousands of awesome companies from over 100 countries. We are a team of humble and talented people who genuinely &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.getharvest.com/blog/2012/05/on-craftsmanship/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;care about our craft&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and demand the highest quality.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;Our customers love Harvest for our great products and legendary support, delivered by our Harvest Experts: wicked-smart human being, empathetic problem-solvers, and patient trouble-shooters.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About You&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re patient and enjoy solving tough problems. You take pride in explaining and helping others understand problems and solutions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re an exceptional communicator and you treat people kindly. You can gracefully break down, solve, and explain, even the most complex problems. Listening, talking, and working with people makes you happy.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Your writing skills are flawless. We mean it. You must have a savvy style and a firm grip on grammar.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You can de-escalate a tense situation with ease and grace—working through a tough issue or bug with an upset customer not only doesn’t scare you, it’s a challenge you’re eager to take on.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re a hard worker with a history of getting things done carefully and efficiently. You’re thorough—no detail go unnoticed. You’re self motivated, but also enjoy contributing to a team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have the ability to switch gears quickly and readjust your focus appropriately.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You don’t mind doing the same thing from day to day. You’re also comfortable jumping onto a side project when the occasion arises and aren’t scared to tackle the new and unknown.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;re happy to work East Coast US business hours of 9am-5pm, give or take an hour in either direction.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What You&amp;#39;ll Do&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learn the ins and outs of Harvest, Harvest Forecast, and are associated apps and integrations.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Answer 20 to 50 customer emails and 10 to 15 phone calls per day.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshoot technical issues in Harvest and help developers diagnose bugs.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Host webinars for and answer questions from prospective Harvest customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Create lively and creative written and video documentation for Harvests Help Center, and keep this documentation up-to-date.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Participate in product development by sharing customer feedback and your unique perspective as a Harvest Expert.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Treat our customers with sincerity, kindness, and respect, and think of new ways to impress, delight, and surprise them.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;To Apply&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Email us at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:customersupport@getharvest.com&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#117;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#109;&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#114;&amp;amp;#115;&amp;amp;#x75;&amp;amp;#112;&amp;amp;#x70;&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x74;&amp;amp;#64;&amp;amp;#x67;&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#116;h&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x76;e&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#46;&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;amp;#109;&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#117;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#109;&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#114;&amp;amp;#115;&amp;amp;#x75;&amp;amp;#112;&amp;amp;#x70;&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x74;&amp;amp;#64;&amp;amp;#x67;&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#116;h&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x76;e&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#46;&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;amp;#109;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; with the subject line &amp;quot;Harvest Expert - _______&amp;quot; (fill in your favorite animal).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tell us a bit about yourself and why you you’d make a great Harvest Expert.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re awesome and can work anywhere… why Harvest?&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Whoops! We made a few grammatical mistakes in this job post. Let us know what they are.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Due to the high volume of applications we receive, we won’t be able to respond to everyone. While we appreciate your enthusiasm, there’s no need to send follow up emails—if we think you’re a good fit for the team, we’ll be in touch!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No phone calls, please.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>LeadFuze Customer Success Manager</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/leadfuze.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 2 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/leadfuze.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since our customers pay us over time, it is imperative that they continue to receive massive value from us.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As such, we need an experienced Customer Success Manager to own the process of helping our customers succeed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This role includes responsibilities for Customer Success activities (e.g., on-boarding, support calls, advising customers on sales strategies, demo calls, adoption, advocacy, retention, etc.) and outcomes (e.g., renewals, up-sell, etc.). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You will need to be based in the United States.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What We Offer:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This position is a remote working opportunity. We will communicate regularly via Slack and through web conferencing solutions such as Google Hangouts, Appear.in, etc. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are able to take as much vacation as you need. We trust our employees! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The pay range is $48,000 to $60,000 per year based on experience with bonuses for hitting certain targets for revenue growth and retention.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Drive Customer Success Outcomes&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Increase renewal rates and reduce churn&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Expand our revenue in accounts through cross-sell and up-sell&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Influence future lifetime value through higher product adoption, customer satisfaction and overall health scores&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Drive new business growth through greater advocacy and reference-ability&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Define and Optimize Customer Lifecycle&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Map customer journey&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Develop listening points in journey (e.g., usage, satisfaction, etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Standardize interventions for each point in journey&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Define segmentation of customer base and varying strategies&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Identify opportunities for continuous improvement&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learn from best practices in industry&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Manage Customer Success Activities&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Onboarding&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Training&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Professional Services&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer Support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer Success Management&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Renewals&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Cross-sell / Up-sell&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Advocacy&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Measure Effectiveness of Customer Success&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Define operational metrics for team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Establish system for tracking metrics&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Create cadence for review within team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Expose subset of metrics to executive team, company and board&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Deliver Sales Related Advice and Strategies to Customers&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understand how sales processes function&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be able to advise our customers who may be in high level roles&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Enhance Effectiveness and Efficiency Through Technology&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Support systems&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer marketing software&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Reference and advocacy solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Create rapid onboarding process for new team members&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Foster collaboration within team and across customer lifecycle&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Delivering webinars on a weekly basis&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Encourage continuous learning within team&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Inspire Customer Success Across Company&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Create company-wide culture of Customer Success&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Align with Marketing around marketing to existing clients&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Align with Product around driving product roadmap&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Align with Sales around cross-sell and up-sell and focus on selling with a retention focus&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Align with Finance around measurement and forecasting&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Align with Executive Team around key metrics and objectives&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Drive company-wide definition of ideal customer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Create company-wide customer feedback loop&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Required Experience / Skills:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;3+ years experience in leading customer-facing organizations&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to manage influence through persuasion, negotiation, and consensus building&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ideally combined background of post-sale account management and sales experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong empathy for customers AND passion for revenue and growth&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Deep understanding of value drivers in recurring revenue business models&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Analytical and process-oriented mindset&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Demonstrated desire for continuous learning and improvement&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiastic and creative leader with the ability to inspire others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience within a software company preferred&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>MailChimp Customer Support Technician - Early Morning Shift</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/mailchimp-early.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/mailchimp-early.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;MailChimp is the world&amp;#39;s leading email marketing service. More than 10 million people and businesses use MailChimp to design and send 1 billion emails a day. We empower small businesses with a suite of powerful and easy-to-use email, marketing automation, and analytics tools that integrate with hundreds of popular applications and services.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;MailChimp’s Customer Support team works around the clock to help users all over the world via chat and email support. Our support agents are extremely smart and slightly weird, and we’re looking to grow their ranks. We’re looking for someone who’s self-motivated, with excellent communications skills and high empathy. Tech-savviness is great, but more important is a strong desire to serve users and a willingness to learn all the ins and outs of the MailChimp app. This position is for our early morning crew, which works Monday through Friday, 5am to 2pm.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Efficiently and effectively answer users’ software and technical questions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Perform root cause analysis and determine appropriate course of action&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Contribute to MailChimp’s Knowledge Base via technical and process support documentation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Identify trends in users’ issues with the app and communicate them to supervisor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Partner with Support team members on strategic projects as needed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Requirements&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;1 or more years experience in technical support and/or customer service&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General curiosity about how and why things work the way they do&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to quickly learn and articulate technical concepts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to empathize with users and convey confidence through written interactions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Well-versed in chat and email etiquette, with a fine-tuned attention to detail&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to multitask and handle multiple support tickets at once&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;MailChimp is a founder-owned, highly profitable, and private company located in the heart of Atlanta. We offer our 500+ employees an exceptional workplace, extremely competitive compensation, fully paid benefits (for employees and their families), and generous profit sharing. We hire humble, collaborative, and ambitious people, and give them endless opportunities to grow and succeed.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We love our hometown and support sustainable urban renewal. Our office is in the historic Ponce City Market, right on the Atlanta Beltline. If you&amp;#39;d like to be considered for this position, please apply below. We look forward to meeting you!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;MailChimp is an equal opportunity employer, and we value diversity at our company. We don’t discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>MailChimp Customer Support Technician - Overnight Shift</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/mailchimp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/mailchimp.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;MailChimp is the world&amp;#39;s leading email marketing service. More than 10 million people and businesses use MailChimp to design and send 1 billion emails a day. We empower small businesses with a suite of powerful and easy-to-use email, marketing automation, and analytics tools that integrate with hundreds of popular applications and services.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;MailChimp’s Customer Support team works around the clock to help users all over the world via chat and email support. Our support agents are extremely smart and slightly weird, and we’re looking to grow their ranks. We’re looking for someone who’s self-motivated, with excellent communications skills and high empathy. Tech-savviness is great, but more important is a strong desire to serve users and a willingness to learn all the ins and outs of the MailChimp app. This position is for our second shift overnight crew, which works Tuesday through Friday, 8pm-6am.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Efficiently and effectively answer users’ software and technical questions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Perform root cause analysis and determine appropriate course of action&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Contribute to MailChimp’s Knowledge Base via technical and process support documentation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Identify trends in users’ issues with the app and communicate them to supervisor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Partner with Support team members on strategic projects as needed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Requirements&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;1 or more years experience in technical support and/or customer service&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General curiosity about how and why things work the way they do&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to quickly learn and articulate technical concepts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to empathize with users and convey confidence through written interactions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Well-versed in chat and email etiquette, with a fine-tuned attention to detail&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to multitask and handle multiple support tickets at once&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;MailChimp is a founder-owned, highly profitable, and private company located in the heart of Atlanta. We offer our 500+ employees an exceptional workplace, extremely competitive compensation, fully paid benefits (for employees and their families), and generous profit sharing. We hire humble, collaborative, and ambitious people, and give them endless opportunities to grow and succeed.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We love our hometown and support sustainable urban renewal. Our office is in the historic Ponce City Market, right on the Atlanta Beltline. If you&amp;#39;d like to be considered for this position, please apply below. We look forward to meeting you!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;MailChimp is an equal opportunity employer, and we value diversity at our company. We don’t discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Segment Success Analyst</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/segment-success.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/segment-success.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our goal is to make life easier for our customers and to leave them with the &amp;quot;wow&amp;quot; feeling of having solved analytics issues with ease, style and class.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;#39;re looking for an experienced customer-facing analyst who loves helping people, solving problems and wants to be a major factor in the success for our customers. This is a perfect position for someone who is somewhat technical and experienced in analytics, but also wants to stay close to customers at a fast-moving startup. If you&amp;#39;ve got a knack for explaining technical concepts this could be a great role for you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a particularly exciting new role at Segment (it&amp;#39;ll be a team of 2 Success Analysts to start) because you&amp;#39;ll be the first point of contact for users of our shiny new &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://segment.com/warehouses&amp;quot;&amp;gt;warehouses&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://segment.com/sources&amp;quot;&amp;gt;sources products&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. You&amp;#39;ll play a key role in the product development process for those products and the creation of our customer success materials.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;d be joining a team of talented engineers and analysts that &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://github.com/segmentio&amp;quot;&amp;gt;love open-source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, supporting their community, and making life easier for people. We care deeply about our users and partners, and we judge ourselves on how well we serve them. So if you enjoy working with smart people and helping to build a company that cares about quality, you&amp;#39;ve found the right place.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Help users get the most out of our new &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://segment.com/warehouses&amp;quot;&amp;gt;warehouses&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://segment.com/sources&amp;quot;&amp;gt;sources&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; products&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide direct support via email and sometimes phone or in person&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take our customer success materials to the next level by writing guides&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work closely with the product team to improve customer success and product development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Become an expert on the Segment platform and the many ways it provides value to analysts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Get A Copywriter Part-Time Account Manager</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/getacopywriter.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/getacopywriter.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We at getacopywriter.com are looking for a part-time Account Manager to join our remote team. This is a long-term opportunity with room for professional growth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The job includes the following:&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Communication with inbound leads&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Work on existing accounts&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Successful candidate must meet the following criteria:&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Be a Native English speaker&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Have experience in Account Executive, Account Manager or Sales roles&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Have a passion to educate and sell to B2B prospects&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Understand importance of content in online marketing&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Have ability to work 10 to 20 hours a week and be available for daily check-ins&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To apply, please include the following:&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Your resume&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- A cover letter outlining your wins in Account Executive, Account Manager or Sales roles&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Get A Copywriter is a one-stop shop to engage talented content writers. With offices in Delaware and Europe, our remote team is successfully supporting blue-chip clients across three continents. Learn more about us at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://getacopywriter.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;getacopywriter.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Formlabs Customer Support Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/formlabs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/formlabs.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To reinvent an industry, you have to build the best team. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Join Formlabs&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; if you want to bring ground-breaking professional 3D printers to the desktop of every designer, engineer, researcher, and artist in the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our primary goal is to give our customers the best tools with an amazing experience. At Formlabs, that means answering every question, no matter how small, and building amazing support material to empower our users to innovate and create.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you love new technology and are a natural problem-solver and a great communicator, we want you on the Form Team as a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Customer Support Engineer&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The job:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Remotely support users in learning the ins and outs of 3D printing&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Keep customers ridiculously happy&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Print in 3D to your heart’s content&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can easily adopt cloud-based business applications&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Power through task lists at lightning speed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can navigate resources to provide answers, even before questions arise&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A critical thinker, with an ability to quickly diagnose and resolve technical issues&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Love going the extra mile to deliver the highest quality care&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Possess exceptional email and phone communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Are a creator: enjoy crafting, forming, making, fabricating, and playing with new tools&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Bonus skills:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience providing technical support for hardware products&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with ticket or case management systems (Zendesk)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with 3D modeling, printing and digital fabrication&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Castle Account Manager</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/castle.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/castle.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your mission will be to care for our owners, tenants, and properties—the core of Castle’s business.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Owners trust us with their properties. Tenants trust us to meet their needs. As an Account Manager, you will nurture the trust of both parties. Specific duties include customer onboarding, marketing properties, moving tenants in (and out), collecting rent, and fielding maintenance requests. You’ll also help supervise a team of Customer Service Representatives.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since Castle is still so young, you should also expect to critically evaluate our processes and makes suggestions for improvement. We believe there is always room to improve, and we need your help making our processes the best they can be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We have a remote-first culture, so we won&amp;#39;t require you to move to Detroit. If you want to move here, or you already live here, you&amp;#39;ll be working out of our headquarters.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You should be:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Detail- and process-oriented&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;A top-flight verbal and written communicator&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;Driven to make everything better&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;A good cop at heart, but a bad cop if need be&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You’ll get:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$40k/year&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;0.025% equity&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Interested? Tell us why you want to join the team at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:fillintheblank@entercastle.com&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:&amp;amp;#102;i&amp;amp;#108;&amp;amp;#108;&amp;amp;#105;n&amp;amp;#116;h&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#98;&amp;amp;#x6c;&amp;amp;#x61;&amp;amp;#110;&amp;amp;#107;@&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#x6e;t&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x63;&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#115;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#108;&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#x2e;&amp;amp;#x63;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#109;&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#102;i&amp;amp;#108;&amp;amp;#108;&amp;amp;#105;n&amp;amp;#116;h&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#98;&amp;amp;#x6c;&amp;amp;#x61;&amp;amp;#110;&amp;amp;#107;@&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#x6e;t&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x63;&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#115;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#108;&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#x2e;&amp;amp;#x63;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#109;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Résumé not necessary.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
