<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support Driven Jobs</title>
    <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jobs.supportdriven.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description>Support Driven Jobs</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:22:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Customer.io Technical Support Engineer (Deliverability Specialist)</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/customerio.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/customerio.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hello, future addition to Customer.io! We’re looking forward to getting to know you better, but you probably want to know what you’re getting yourself into. You can check out our careers page, or read on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At Customer.io, our mission is helping businesses talk like people. Today, we do this with messaging software that allows businesses with large user-bases to send targeted, more relevant communication at scale.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;A day in the life of a Deliverability Specialist&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A Deliverability Specialist at Customer.io helps new and existing customers get up and running in our product, diagnose tricky situations related to email deliverability, and achieve their business goals. Our customers are core to everything we do (it’s in our name!) and a Deliverability Specialist on our Technical Support Team has contact with more customers than anyone else in the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What skills will you bring to the table?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First and foremost, we’re looking for someone with experience diagnosing and solving email deliverability issues. We’re also looking for some customer support experience, responding mainly via email within a remote/async environment. Ideally you’ve worked with or supported email marketing/business communication tools, too. You should be comfortable with basic programming concepts (API, variables, if-else statements, loops, etc.). You’re willing to work in US Eastern hours on a regular basis.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Your contributions to the team will include:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;being the expert on the team for any deliverability questions or problems our customers may have&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;identifying ways deliverability rates can be higher including working with partner sites and services to mitigate the risk of any future blacklisting.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;establishing tools that can monitor the list of our IP addresses to proactively head off any blacklist issues.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;building processes and procedures to ensure the entire team can work seamlessly to help our customers when deliverability issues arise.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Beyond your focus on deliverability, you’ll develop deep product, systems and customer knowledge by supporting our customers via email. You’ll also work on internal and external documentation and have regular touch points with our Product and Development teams to discuss feature requests, usability issues and user scenarios. You’ll bring your passion for customers and their problems to advocate for product improvements and provide insight that will help us make sure we build the right thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the long run there are opportunities to apply that to automate processes and create internal tools or to join our Customer Success team which helps our high revenue customers make the most of our product. We have many new features to build and ideas to implement, so there will be plenty of exciting challenges ahead.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today the Technical Support team is powered by Help Scout for tickets, Github Issues for bug tracking and Zapier to help automate some of our support processes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although, we mostly interact with each other through Basecamp and Slack and value focused work, we’re not afraid to jump on a Screenhero pairing session or a video call to clarify customer scenarios or share tips on how to troubleshoot issues better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You’ll be joining a team of 4 including:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Wendy Teo&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; - Director of Technical Support - lovingly referred to as unicorn because she’s fantastic AND elusive (we rarely get to see her whole face)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And our Technical Support Engineers:&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Brandi Young&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; - resident Texan, considers eminem her guilty pleasure and is perfectly introverted and awkward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Wiley Jenkins&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; - from coffee stand to tech, and most recently, Customer.io; Wiley will make you smile.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Dan Schales&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; - Star Wars expert, enjoying family life in Washington State; Dan’s the support(man).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The folks above are an incredible group, and we’re excited for you to meet them. If you’re still reading this, then you’ll share some qualities with them like:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You love technical problem solving&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You enjoy helping others with your technical knowledge and take pride in your work.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You see every support ticket as an opportunity to improve the customer experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You take ownership of delivering results and get satisfaction from getting things done.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re passionate about learning new things.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re not afraid to ask questions if you’re confused about how something works.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You understand written communication is not always perfect and assume the best intentions during interactions with customers and your team. Empathy is one of your strongest attributes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Why should you work with Customer.io?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We want to enable you to do your best work, and this is how we aim to do that—&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Salary:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; We’re offering $70,000 USD for this position in the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Equity:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; You’ll own a piece of the company. It&amp;#39;s not a get-rich-quick deal, but if you stay around for a while, we&amp;#39;re planning to be a long-lasting company, and your piece of it may be a nice bonus.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Big impact:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; Our team is small, but growing quickly. The work you do will materially impact how successful we are as a company, both with our product and our culture.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Great tools:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; Everyone in the company has a budget for a great computer, motorized standing desk, Steelcase Leap office chair, external monitor, and anything else you&amp;#39;d like to get your job done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Health benefits:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; We pay 100% of your premiums for medical, dental and vision.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Paid Parental &amp;amp;amp; Medical Leave&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; - including adoption&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Retreats:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; We want everyone in our company to connect in person whenever possible, so we get everyone together once a year. We&amp;#39;ve had retreats in Barcelona, Romania, and Hunter Mountain, NY. We’re going to Iceland in September!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Vacation:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; Rest and recuperation are important. We offer unlimited paid time off with a two week minimum per year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Diversity at Customer.io&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At Customer.io, we’re committed to building a diverse environment, and encourage minority applicants. So far, we have team members in Scotland, Germany, Canada, and all over the US. Our CEO and CTO grew up in Singapore and Arkansas respectively, but met in New York City. Our company culture is always evolving; people from different backgrounds bring valued perspective and thoughtfulness to the work that we do and the culture we foster.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Customer.io provides equal employment opportunities (EEO) to all employees and applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability or genetics. In addition to federal law requirements, Customer.io complies with applicable state and local laws governing nondiscrimination in employment in every location in which the company has facilities. This policy applies to all terms and conditions of employment, including recruiting, hiring, placement, promotion, termination, layoff, recall, transfer, leaves of absence, compensation and training. Basically, we follow the law, but also like you for who you are!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Intrigued? Talk to us!&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apply below with your resume, and make sure you tell us why you’re interested in the position! We’ve added a few questions that will also help us understand how you think.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Accounts Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-accounts-au.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-accounts-au.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Accounts Support team is looking for a full-time team member who is based in the Asia Pacific region. This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in the Asia Pacific region, so legal working authorisation is required: Japan, Australia, and New Zealand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they email support. We help people as quickly and awesomely as possible. Our Account Support team handle passwords, email verification, billing, legal, spam and abuse, account lockouts, fraud, and helping people choose plans. This requires a logical brain and a spidey sense for solving problems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Developers: this probably isn&amp;#39;t the job for you, but perhaps you have a friend who would be a perfect fit. Send them this link. Thanks!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in Japan, Australia or New Zealand.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal working authorisation to work in Japan, Australia or New Zealand.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills – you might not know all of the answers, but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy and the ability to advocate for others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer support experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, elaborate boardgames)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Previous work with GitHub and/or developers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of banking or online payment systems&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience supporting web apps&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Accounts Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-accounts-jp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-accounts-jp.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Accounts Support team is looking for a full-time team member who is based in the Asia Pacific region. This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in the Asia Pacific region, so legal working authorisation is required: Japan, Australia, and New Zealand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they email support. We help people as quickly and awesomely as possible. Our Account Support team handle passwords, email verification, billing, legal, spam and abuse, account lockouts, fraud, and helping people choose plans. This requires a logical brain and a spidey sense for solving problems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Developers: this probably isn&amp;#39;t the job for you, but perhaps you have a friend who would be a perfect fit. Send them this link. Thanks!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in Japan, Australia or New Zealand.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal working authorisation to work in Japan, Australia or New Zealand.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills – you might not know all of the answers, but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy and the ability to advocate for others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer support experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, elaborate boardgames)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Previous work with GitHub and/or developers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of banking or online payment systems&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience supporting web apps&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Accounts Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-accounts-nz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-accounts-nz.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Accounts Support team is looking for a full-time team member who is based in the Asia Pacific region. This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in the Asia Pacific region, so legal working authorisation is required: Japan, Australia, and New Zealand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they email support. We help people as quickly and awesomely as possible. Our Account Support team handle passwords, email verification, billing, legal, spam and abuse, account lockouts, fraud, and helping people choose plans. This requires a logical brain and a spidey sense for solving problems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Developers: this probably isn&amp;#39;t the job for you, but perhaps you have a friend who would be a perfect fit. Send them this link. Thanks!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in Japan, Australia or New Zealand.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal working authorisation to work in Japan, Australia or New Zealand.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills – you might not know all of the answers, but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy and the ability to advocate for others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer support experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, elaborate boardgames)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Previous work with GitHub and/or developers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of banking or online payment systems&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience supporting web apps&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Enterprise Support Agent</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-esa-au.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-esa-au.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More and more companies are using GitHub Enterprise, so the support team is growing. When our customers have problems, they contact us and it is our goal to help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. We&amp;#39;re looking for Enterprise Support Agents to join our Asia Pacific Support team. This role is remote, but candidates must be currently be located in Australia, Japan, or New Zealand and possess legal working authorization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The position reports to an Enterprise Support Manager and works closely with other teams and leaders across the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub works remotely and asynchronously as much as possible. While this role does not require you to live near our office, it will require some travel to meet with co-workers or attend company events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take in-bound phone support requests&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Triage incoming support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work collaboratively with other support teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Manage communication around customer tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshoot and help solve highly complex support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Escalate issues to other support engineers and managers as applicable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Engineering team to prioritize issues and development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Documentation team to improve customer-facing resources&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal and working authorization in New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of Linux servers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General understanding of how modern web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiasm for working directly with customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to clearly write and orally communicate technical information&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to review and understand code (Ruby / Bash)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must have a workspace conducive to answering phone calls&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior experience providing technical support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong empathy for GitHub users and GitHub Support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, systems administration, etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with Git and GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Enterprise Support Agent</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-esa-eu.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-esa-eu.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More and more companies are using GitHub Enterprise, so the support team is growing. When our customers have problems, they contact us and it is our goal to help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. We&amp;#39;re looking for Enterprise Support Agents to join our Europe Support team. This role is remote, but candidates must be currently be located in Austria, Croatia (also called Hrvatska), Denmark, France, Germany, Ireland, Netherlands, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, or United Kingdom and possess legal working authorization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The position reports to an Enterprise Support Manager and works closely with other teams and leaders across the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub works remotely and asynchronously as much as possible. While this role does not require you to live near our office, it will require some travel to meet with co-workers or attend company events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take in-bound phone support requests&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Triage incoming support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work collaboratively with other support teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Manage communication around customer tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshoot and help solve highly complex support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Escalate issues to other support engineers and managers as applicable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Engineering team to prioritize issues and development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Documentation team to improve customer-facing resources&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal and working authorization in New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of Linux servers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General understanding of how modern web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiasm for working directly with customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to clearly write and orally communicate technical information&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to review and understand code (Ruby / Bash)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must have a workspace conducive to answering phone calls&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior experience providing technical support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong empathy for GitHub users and GitHub Support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, systems administration, etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with Git and GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Enterprise Support Agent</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-esa-jp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-esa-jp.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More and more companies are using GitHub Enterprise, so the support team is growing. When our customers have problems, they contact us and it is our goal to help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. We&amp;#39;re looking for Enterprise Support Agents to join our Asia Pacific Support team. This role is remote, but candidates must be currently be located in Australia, Japan, or New Zealand and possess legal working authorization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The position reports to an Enterprise Support Manager and works closely with other teams and leaders across the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub works remotely and asynchronously as much as possible. While this role does not require you to live near our office, it will require some travel to meet with co-workers or attend company events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take in-bound phone support requests&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Triage incoming support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work collaboratively with other support teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Manage communication around customer tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshoot and help solve highly complex support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Escalate issues to other support engineers and managers as applicable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Engineering team to prioritize issues and development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Documentation team to improve customer-facing resources&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal and working authorization in New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of Linux servers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General understanding of how modern web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiasm for working directly with customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to clearly write and orally communicate technical information&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to review and understand code (Ruby / Bash)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must have a workspace conducive to answering phone calls&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior experience providing technical support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong empathy for GitHub users and GitHub Support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, systems administration, etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with Git and GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Enterprise Support Agent</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-esa-nz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-esa-nz.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More and more companies are using GitHub Enterprise, so the support team is growing. When our customers have problems, they contact us and it is our goal to help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. We&amp;#39;re looking for Enterprise Support Agents to join our Asia Pacific Support team. This role is remote, but candidates must be currently be located in Australia, Japan, or New Zealand and possess legal working authorization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The position reports to an Enterprise Support Manager and works closely with other teams and leaders across the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub works remotely and asynchronously as much as possible. While this role does not require you to live near our office, it will require some travel to meet with co-workers or attend company events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take in-bound phone support requests&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Triage incoming support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work collaboratively with other support teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Manage communication around customer tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshoot and help solve highly complex support tickets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Escalate issues to other support engineers and managers as applicable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Engineering team to prioritize issues and development&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with our Documentation team to improve customer-facing resources&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal and working authorization in New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge of Linux servers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General understanding of how modern web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiasm for working directly with customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to clearly write and orally communicate technical information&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to review and understand code (Ruby / Bash)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must have a workspace conducive to answering phone calls&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior experience providing technical support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong empathy for GitHub users and GitHub Support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical experience (QA, documentation, systems administration, etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with Git and GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Enterprise Support Engineer; Japanese Language</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-ese-jp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-ese-jp.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub is looking for full-time Enterprise Support Engineers to provide Japanese-language support for our customers in Japan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More and more companies are using GitHub Enterprise, so our global Enterprise Support Team is quickly growing. When our customers have problems, they contact us and it is our goal to help them as quickly, and awesomely as possible. We&amp;#39;re looking for Japanese language Enterprise Support Engineers to join our Asia Pacific Support team. This role is remote, but candidates must currently be located in Australia, Japan, or New Zealand and possess legal working authorization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At GitHub, we take support seriously, and this is not an entry-level position. Our Enterprise Support Engineers are responsible for helping our GitHub Enterprise customers who have our product installed and managed in the customer&amp;#39;s virtualization environment. Your main responsibility will be to work with our customers to solve support tickets. Tickets are usually opened by internal system administrators, and can include investigating load or networking issues, debugging application errors, and discussing feature requests. You&amp;#39;ll also work with our engineering team to prioritize issues and development, and our documentation team to improve customer-facing resources. You don’t need to be a Git expert, but you do need to have technical experience and a passion for helping people.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The position reports to an Enterprise Support Manager and works closely with other teams and leaders across the company. GitHub works remotely and asynchronously as much as possible. While this role does not require you to live near one of our offices, it will require some travel to meet with co-workers or attend company events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Solve complex customer support tickets often involving Linux servers, source code, and web application issues&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Effectively communicate technical information to customers and engineering groups at GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work proactively with customers on activities such as coordinating upgrades, communicating upcoming features, and ensuring their installation is running smoothly&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Identify bugs and improvements in the GitHub Enterprise codebase&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Manage urgent customer outages during business hours&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Current legal working authorization in Japan&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with Linux&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;General understanding of how modern web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior experience providing technical support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem-solving skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with some flavor of production-level virtual machine (e.g., VMware ESX, Xen, KVM)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiasm for working directly with customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar Japanese and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Business level English skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Worked closely with large complex customer accounts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with Git and GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with phone support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The ability to look through and understand code (Ruby / Bash)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Previous experience as a Linux System Administrator&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Previous experience providing on-site consulting or professional services&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Technical Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-tss-au.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-tss-au.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Technical Support team is looking for full-time team members located in Asia Pacific. This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in Asia Pacific, so legal working authorization is required: Japan, Australia, and New Zealand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub users work 24/7, so you&amp;#39;ll occasionally need to adjust your work week to help cover a weekend or holiday (don&amp;#39;t worry! We strongly support flexible schedules that let you take care of the important things in your life).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they contact Support and we help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. Technical support handles a wide variety of inquiries including questions about Git and GitHub workflows, GitHub Pages, our API, and our desktop applications. Support also works closely with the engineering team to track down bugs and improve our documentation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in addition to legal working authorization to work in Japan, Australia, or New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience using GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exposure to programming with a language like Ruby&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Basic experience using Git&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understanding of how websites and web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem-solving skills – you might not know all the answers but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy – you are attuned to hear the question behind a question&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Will love developers and GitHub as much as we do&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Could effortlessly explain how Git works to a non-developer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have remote customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working from the command line&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiar with basic network concepts and tools&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Technical Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-tss-jp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-tss-jp.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Technical Support team is looking for full-time team members located in Asia Pacific. This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in Asia Pacific, so legal working authorization is required: Japan, Australia, and New Zealand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub users work 24/7, so you&amp;#39;ll occasionally need to adjust your work week to help cover a weekend or holiday (don&amp;#39;t worry! We strongly support flexible schedules that let you take care of the important things in your life).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they contact Support and we help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. Technical support handles a wide variety of inquiries including questions about Git and GitHub workflows, GitHub Pages, our API, and our desktop applications. Support also works closely with the engineering team to track down bugs and improve our documentation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in addition to legal working authorization to work in Japan, Australia, or New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience using GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exposure to programming with a language like Ruby&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Basic experience using Git&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understanding of how websites and web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem-solving skills – you might not know all the answers but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy – you are attuned to hear the question behind a question&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Will love developers and GitHub as much as we do&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Could effortlessly explain how Git works to a non-developer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have remote customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working from the command line&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiar with basic network concepts and tools&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>GitHub Technical Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/github-tss-nz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/github-tss-nz.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The GitHub Technical Support team is looking for full-time team members located in Asia Pacific. This person will join GitHub as part of our global support team and support our customers around the world. This is the current list of countries in which we are set up as an employer in Asia Pacific, so legal working authorization is required: Japan, Australia, and New Zealand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GitHub users work 24/7, so you&amp;#39;ll occasionally need to adjust your work week to help cover a weekend or holiday (don&amp;#39;t worry! We strongly support flexible schedules that let you take care of the important things in your life).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When GitHub users have questions, they contact Support and we help them as quickly and awesomely as possible. Technical support handles a wide variety of inquiries including questions about Git and GitHub workflows, GitHub Pages, our API, and our desktop applications. Support also works closely with the engineering team to track down bugs and improve our documentation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important characteristic of our support team is that we love helping developers. GitHub is a place for people to work better, together. Our job is to help. Support treats users the way we&amp;#39;d want someone to treat our friends.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our support teammates have excellent writing chops: stellar grammar, charming written personality, and the ability to explain complicated things simply. We measure our success in swiftness, accuracy, and clarity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Minimum Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Currently residing in addition to legal working authorization to work in Japan, Australia, or New Zealand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience using GitHub&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exposure to programming with a language like Ruby&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Basic experience using Git&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understanding of how websites and web applications work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stellar English and grammar skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent problem-solving skills – you might not know all the answers but you know how to find and communicate the solution&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A strong sense of empathy – you are attuned to hear the question behind a question&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A unique writing style and voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Preferred Qualifications:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Will love developers and GitHub as much as we do&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Could effortlessly explain how Git works to a non-developer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have remote customer service experience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working from the command line&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiar with basic network concepts and tools&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>SolarWinds Cloud (Librato, Papertrail, &amp; Pingdom) Product Advocate / Technical Account Manager</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/solarwinds-cloud.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/solarwinds-cloud.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Product Advocate, you’ll use technical experience, product knowledge, and sales skills to help every customer get the most value from SolarWinds’ Monitoring Cloud (SaaS) products:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Librato (infrastructure monitoring): &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.librato.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://www.librato.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Papertrail (log-centric troubleshooting): &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://papertrailapp.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://papertrailapp.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Pingdom (Web performance): &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.pingdom.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://www.pingdom.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;TraceView (application performance monitoring) : &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://traceview.solarwinds.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://traceview.solarwinds.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you’ve made a restaurant reservation, collaborated in a text chat room, or purchased a plane ticket, you probably used a service which depends on SolarWinds Monitoring Cloud.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Why is this role important?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your customers, many of whom are fellow engineers, will come to see you as a trusted peer. You’ll be instrumental in figuring out what types of technical account management actually help, why, and how to scale it. This is an incredibly fast-growing market. As the SolarWinds Monitoring Cloud thrives and expands in the coming years, you’ll have contributed significantly to that growth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Why is this position unique?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Big company benefits and customer base, startup flexibility. As Product Advocate, you’ll:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;be the primary contact for your customers, not just a sales engineer. If you’re equally adept at cloning a git repo as you are at explaining why a product is valuable enough to pay for, this role is for you.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;have an unusual amount of control over which actions may be worth your time. We’ll be brainstorming, selecting, and testing these together.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;see the impact of your work every day – not in 0.1% of customers, but in 10% or 30% of customers. If something is demonstrably effective, you’ll help implement or share it widely.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;sell products that you’d actually use yourself. Life is too short to represent a product you don’t care about.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;sell products which already have thousands of satisfied customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;interact with customers using newer technologies like Docker, Go, React, and Kubernetes as well as established products like PostgreSQL, nginx, and Heroku.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Qualifications&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Technical expertise, so you can be useful to software developers and systems engineers. Perhaps you’ve been a sales engineer, customer success engineer, technical account manager or thrived in a “dev bootcamp” program. Maybe you’re writing code now and want a change.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Able to confidently explain that something costs money (and why!), and ideally, past experience in a sales role. If you have a demonstrated interest in business (like sales, entrepreneurship, or finance), even as a hobby, we want to hear.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re great at explaining complex ideas in writing. This position is 80% email or text, 20% interactive (voice or video)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Able to confidently give a screenshare-style product demo that attendees enjoy&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You value the chance to help define the process. In past roles, maybe you’ve had strong opinions about how sales could do a better job or how you could do a better job if you were the sales rep.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Nice to have: Experience interacting with engineers on a daily basis (such as by selling a product to engineers or supporting a product used by engineers), and/or working with a distributed team (such as in Slack)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Examples of technical expertise&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Part of this job is identifying customer-specific use cases and opportunities where these products can be more helpful and thus get used more. These are usually technical conversations. To add value, you’ve probably done at least 1 of these 5 tasks or something very similar:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;modified a Ruby, Python, Unix shell, or other script/code to do what you want or run correctly (or, of course, written your own)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;cloned a git repo and committed a change&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;used a somewhat advanced command-line tool like tcpdump, strace, ntop, iptables, or awk&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;booted a Docker container or EC2/Xen instance&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;configured a daemon like rsyslog or sshd&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Want to stand out?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sign up for a SolarWinds Monitoring Cloud product (like Librato, Papertrail, or Pingdom), then write an email or record a screencast demo for an imaginary customer. In the email or screencast, explain why this product is a better fit than competitors.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
