<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support Driven Jobs</title>
    <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jobs.supportdriven.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description>Support Driven Jobs</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 11:09:52 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 11:09:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Customer.io Technical Support Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/customerio.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/customerio.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hello, future addition to Customer.io! We’re looking forward to getting to know you better, but you probably want to know what you’re getting yourself into. You can check out our careers page, or read on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At Customer.io, our mission is helping businesses talk like people. Today, we do this with messaging software that allows businesses with large user-bases to send targeted, more relevant communication at scale. Our customers include Shutterstock, DigitalOcean, Handy, and Watsi.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;A day in the life of a Technical Support Engineer&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A Technical Support Engineer at Customer.io helps new and existing customers get up and running in our product, diagnose tricky situations in the product, and achieve their business goals. Our customers are core to everything we do (it’s in our name!) and a Technical Support Engineer has contact with more customers than anyone else in the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While support tickets may take most of your day, you’ll also work on internal and external documentation and have regular touch points with our Product and Customer Success teams to discuss feature requests, usability issues and user scenarios. You’ll bring your passion for customers and their problems to advocate for product improvements and provide insight that will help us make sure we build the right thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Technical Support Engineers develop deep product, systems and customer knowledge. In the long run there are opportunities to apply that to automate processes and create internal tools or to join our Customer Success team which helps our high revenue customers make the most of our product. We have many new features to build and ideas to implement, so there will be plenty of exciting challenges ahead.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today the Technical Support team is powered by Help Scout for tickets, Github Issues for bug tracking and Zapier to help automate some of our support processes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although, we mostly interact with each other through Basecamp and Slack and value focused work, we’re not afraid to jump on a Screenhero pairing session or a video call to clarify customer scenarios or share tips on how to troubleshoot issues better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;We’re the right match for you if:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You love technical problem solving&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You enjoy helping others with your technical knowledge and take pride in your work.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You see every support ticket as an opportunity to improve the customer experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You take ownership of delivering results and get satisfaction from getting things done.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re passionate about learning new things.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re not afraid to ask questions if you’re confused about how something works.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You understand written communication is not always perfect and assume the best intentions during interactions with customers and your team. Empathy is one of your strongest attributes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What we look for:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;At least 2 years customer support experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working remotely (it’s not your first time holding a full-time or part-time remote job).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;HTML &amp;amp;amp; CSS knowledge (just enough to troubleshoot and fix issues reported by customers).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understanding of basic programming concepts (API, variables, if-else statements, loops, etc.). If you know some Javascript too even better!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working with or supporting email marketing/ business communication tools preferred.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Located in the United States/ Canada or willing to work US Eastern or Pacific hours.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Why should you work with Customer.io?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We want to enable you to do your best work, and this is how we aim to do that—&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Salary:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; We are offering salary of $70,000 USD for this position.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Equity:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; You’ll own a piece of the company. It&amp;#39;s not a get-rich-quick deal, but if you stay around for a while, we&amp;#39;re planning to be a long-lasting company, and your piece of it may be a nice bonus.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Big impact:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; Our team is small, but growing quickly. The work you do will materially impact how successful we are as a company, both with our product and our culture.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Great tools:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; Everyone in the company has a budget for a great computer, motorized standing desk, Steelcase Leap office chair, external monitor, and anything else you&amp;#39;d like to get your job done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Health benefits:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; We pay 100% of your premiums for medical, dental and vision.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Retreats:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; We want everyone in our company to connect in person whenever possible, so we get everyone together once a year. We&amp;#39;ve had retreats in Barcelona, Romania, and Hunter Mountain, NY.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Vacation:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; Rest and recuperation are important. We offer unlimited paid time off with a two week minimum per year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Diversity at Customer.io&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At Customer.io, we’re committed to building a diverse environment, and encourage minority applicants. So far, we have team members in Scotland, Germany, Canada, and all over the US. Our CEO and CTO grew up in Singapore and Arkansas respectively, but met in New York City. Our company culture is always evolving; people from different backgrounds bring valued perspective and thoughtfulness to the work that we do and the culture we foster.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Customer.io provides equal employment opportunities (EEO) to all employees and applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability or genetics. In addition to federal law requirements, Customer.io complies with applicable state and local laws governing nondiscrimination in employment in every location in which the company has facilities. This policy applies to all terms and conditions of employment, including recruiting, hiring, placement, promotion, termination, layoff, recall, transfer, leaves of absence, compensation and training. Basically, we follow the law, but also like you for who you are!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Intrigued? Talk to us!&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apply with your resume, and make sure you tell us why you’re interested in the position! We’ve added a few questions that will also help us understand how you think.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>EventMobi Support Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/eventmobi.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 8 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/eventmobi.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EventMobi is changing the way event planners create, market and manage their events, as well as how attendees experience events using their smartphones and tablets for thousands of events, conferences and tradeshows around the world. Clients like Motorola, Ralph Lauren, Nestle, Intel and Canadian Heart &amp;amp;amp; Stroke Foundation have used EventMobi to enhance the attendee experience at their events.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Want to quickly figure out what EventMobi is all about? Then watch this fun 3min video here: &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.eventmobi.com/careers/#video&amp;quot;&amp;gt;http://www.eventmobi.com/careers/#video&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wondering how our technology is affecting the world and the meeting industry in general? Well here is an awesome infographic that summarizes what we have achieved this past and why we are super excited for 2016: &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.eventmobi.com/about/company/2015/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;http://www.eventmobi.com/about/company/2015/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What impact will you have?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;First point of contact for our amazing clients when they need help - Our clients are generally professional event planners working at associations or large corporations. -The end user of our product however are attendees around the world from all ages and professions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Lead client onboarding process from end-to-end&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Handle inquiries about app development and troubleshoot client needs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take accountability to solve issues from beginning to end.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Liaise with Engineering team to help drive feature development for our product&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Receive and incorporate client feedback to improve business performance&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proactively profile customer needs and match our products and services to those needs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;This is a chance to learn and be involved at every point of the company while helping and building relationships with a wide range of EventMobi clients across the world.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;10% travel is required: our clients often need our support team to help in the execution of their event&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Limited evening and weekend work may be required to help with peak times based on client needs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What will you bring to the team?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;An empathetic desire to help: For you, a new inquiry isn’t a just case to close, but an opportunity to understand someone’s story and make their life better. Our purpose as a company is to help event planners thrive.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Superb communication skills: You understand that effective communication is about more than what you say, it’s about taking the time to listen and understand. You can make complicated concepts sound easy or describe in detail the simplest of interactions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A deep understanding of software and the web: You won’t need to know how to code, but terms like HTML and CSS shouldn’t be foreign to you. You can quickly learn complex procedures, troubleshoot potential bugs on the fly (pun intended), and visualize customers’ screens from their description alone.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior customer facing experience: Whether it was building a rapport with customers at Starbucks/Apple, or working in a customer-centric call centre, you must have experience working with customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong interpersonal skills - ability to work with people with a variety of skill sets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can you make good choices that serve both the customer and company? We need folks who are passionate about delighting and retaining customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Aircall Customer Support Hero</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/aircall.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/aircall.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;ll join the US business team to ensure that the customers we work with have a great experience. You will be the first point of contact and advocate for clients.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What are the responsibilities:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be the voice of Aircall - you will be on the front lines! This involves flexing your amazing troubleshooting skills via phone calls, emails, and live chat.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide swift and thorough solutions for customers. When absolutely unable to do so, escalate to the dev/tech team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Take note and relay customer feedback and insights to Aircall&amp;#39;s internal teams such as the tech, marketing and product teams, in order to constantly improve the customer experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Maintain an expert-level knowledge of our products and internal management systems as well as curiosity and awareness of new initiatives within in the industry.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What we are looking for:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have at least 1+ year of experience in Support and are passionate about it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are technical and problem solver. UDP/TCP ports, REST API and packet losses do mean something to you.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have a “no task is too small” attitude and the endurance to consistently deliver amazing customer experiences without exception.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have superior written and oral communication skills.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have strong people skills — you are friendly, a good listener, you ask good questions, and you&amp;#39;re energized by personal interaction.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You are a team player who works well with a wide range of personalities and is ready to contribute to an awesome team environment.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Brownie points:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have a sense of humour and know how to make fun of yourself.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flexibility with schedule to meet the needs of the business.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What are the benefits of working here?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;All the caffeine you need to keep you going&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Medical/Vision/Dental benefits&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tax-free commuter benefits&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Your metrocard reimbursed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Gym reimbursement&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Shiny new Mac gear!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Automattic Happiness Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/automattic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/automattic.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Happiness Engineer, helping people is your passion. Maybe you’ve developed your own support philosophy by reading books like Delivering Happiness or Exceptional Service, Exceptional Profit. Perhaps you’re a contributor in an online support community such as the &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums or &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Transforming publishing on the web is no small task. Our goal is to build relationships based on trust which result in happy, passionate, loyal customers and colleagues. We do this through listening to their needs and guiding them to the fullest use of the products we offer. We are looking for people with the right mix of compassion, writing skills, and technical knowledge to get the job done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;In general, a typical day involves:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Helping people use Automattic’s products, including &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, WooCommerce, Jetpack, Gravatar, and more&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshooting, investigating, and creating detailed bug reports&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Crafting and editing helpful support documentation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being an active member of a team that provides around the clock support to our users via live chat, forums, and email&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Building a community of support by sharing knowledge and insight amongst team members&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Being a Happiness Engineer requires:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Patience, grace, and a sense of humor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent writing and communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working knowledge of WordPress, HTML, and CSS&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A knack for taking technical language and making it understandable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A passion for solving tough problems and proposing elegant solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happiness Engineers must be fluent and eloquent in written English. If you know additional languages, be sure to tell us!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums are fantastic places to gain the experience required for this position. If you are already active there, let us know! Send a link to your forum profile and we’ll check it out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
