<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support Driven Jobs</title>
    <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jobs.supportdriven.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description>Support Driven Jobs</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 14:19:04 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 14:19:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Fastly Customer Support Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/fastly.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/fastly.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fastly is a flexible, transparent content delivery network that accelerates and scales websites, mobile applications, and APIs. We do this by moving content physically closer to a company’s end users. If you’re tweeting, pinning, shopping on Wayfair or ModCloth, reading the news on Fast Company or The Guardian, browsing pictures on Imgur, or coding with GitHub, Fastly is improving your user experience.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The global CDN market is estimated to grow from $3.71 billion in 2014 to $12.16 billion in 2019. With an exciting product roadmap and a fast-growing international team, Fastly is redefining what’s possible online.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We’re building a better Internet. Come join us. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;CUSTOMER SUPPORT ENGINEER&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fastly’s goal of creating the best set of tools for people who scale the internet is rooted in great support. It&amp;#39;s a core value, and something that shapes our culture. Fastly is looking for passionate support engineers to continue our high standard of support, as well scale and improve our support systems as we grow.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The ideal candidate should be a master of written voice, and have the technical curiosity and experience necessary to understand Fastly’s product from end to end. They’ll be working with our marketing, engineering, and sales teams on behalf of our customer base, so a passion for customer advocacy is essential. Also, no two support tickets at Fastly are alike, so support engineers will be dealing with a wide range of complex and rewarding problems on a daily basis.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Assist with customer CDN configurations over email and chat&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Communicate customer needs and requirements with the engineering, product and sales teams&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Contribute to our customer facing documentation when necessary&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Contribute to the processes and policies that scale our support organization as we grow&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;REQUIREMENTS&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with a *nix environment
&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with one or more programming languages&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to debug connections using cURL, traceroute, telnet and other network diagnostic tools&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Prior CDN, support, or sysadmin experience a plus&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>ProTrainings Customer Happiness Hero</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/protrainings.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/protrainings.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You...&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Are good at seeing things from other people’s point of view&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strive to take care of others like you would take care of your own family&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Love to build relationships with customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Want to take customer care to the next level&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Emulate other companies that provide amazing service: Disney, Chick-Fil-A, Nordstrom, Ritz-Carlton, Trader Joe’s, and Zappos are some great examples&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;See the value in having a rabid, loyal customer base&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Embrace change&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Push for excellence&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Who we are&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We’ve been certifying people in CPR, first aid, and bloodborne pathogens since 2003. Not only that -- we’ve been increasing in size, training more people, adding more trainings, and getting bigger and stronger every year since.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are a collaborative, growing team that creates and supports the world’s best training. Our online health and safety courses help save lives every day (literally -- we have heard countless stories from our customers who have saved the lives of loved ones after using our training).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We work out of an awesome, open building in Grand Rapids, Michigan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What we believe&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Providing life-saving training is a noble pursuit that is worth getting up every morning to create.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We believe that every team member is crucial and makes a difference, which is why we hire highly-motivated, hard-working, well-rounded people who pursue excellence in everything they do. That’s also why we’re very selective and particular about hiring great people, especially in this position, as you will be the face of our company to many of our customers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We think that surprising and delighting our customers at every turn makes life-long, loyal supporters who rave about you to their friends; not to mention, it helps make the world a better place to live!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We believe that training should be FREE, because nobody should have to take out their wallet to learn how to save a life. In fact, we believe this so strongly, we created a StudentCPR program that trains thousands of high school students every single year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We believe that you can work really hard and still have a ton of fun. You can play ping pong to blow off steam, chat with customers from our ceiling suspended hammock chair, and play games with co-workers at the office at night. Work and fun are not mutually exclusive -- having a good work-life balance is critical to loving your job and doing great work.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We love innovation. We don’t like to do things like everyone else. A great example is our Single Use Manikin Option (SUMO). For the first time in the history of CPR training, people are able to complete their entire certification without leaving home.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What you’ll be doing&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Delighting our customers by forming real relationships with them (through phone, email, and chat), including sending out postcards and follow-up emails to show our appreciation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Forming meaningful relationships with company administrators (Nike, Bed Bath &amp;amp;amp; Beyond, Goodwill, and Jazzercise are just a few companies that use us) while assisting them with setup, onboarding, and follow-up&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Providing insightful advice and friendly support to ProTrainings customers in need&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Quickly diagnosing problems on the spot, determining and explaining situations with patience and empathy so our customers can get trained and get back to work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Taking ownership of every customer interaction -- we empower you to make decisions and care for customers in creative ways -- no robots here&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Collaborating with other departments to WOW our customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learning and growing professionally by taking time every week to read articles or books from our bookshelf to better yourself&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working 12pm - 8pm or 9am - 5pm (EST) with the possibility of alternating shift coverage&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We are open to remote workers who have a great work ethic, are self-motivated, and do great work without direct supervision&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Desired experience&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You have worked in a customer-relations role in the past, whether that was as a receptionist, a call center rep, nursing assistant, barista, bank teller, anything in retail, or any other position in which you helped and delighted customers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Basic skills we’re looking for&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong writing skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong people skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A good speaking voice&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to maintain composure and customer focus while troubleshooting and solving technical issues&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Comfortable with technology&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fast typer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Comfortable on phone, email, and chat&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fast learner&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Attention to detail&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bonus if you are able to speak Spanish (at least at a high school level) and interested in learning more&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Benefits you’ll love&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Health / dental insurance&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Paid time off&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;401k with company match&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fun culture / atmosphere&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A career that makes a difference (train people to save lives, hear heroic stories, and receive awesome testimonials from really grateful customers)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;High level of autonomy and creativity while helping and delighting customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Extensive, continuous training (you won’t be thrown in blind)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Professional development library (request a book or resource, and you’ll have it within 2 weeks)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;CPR / first aid training &amp;amp;amp; certification&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Ready to help save lives?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you’re still reading this, we would love to learn more about you. Shoot an email to careers at protrainings dot com and include the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A fun, catchy subject line&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Your top 3 strengths&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A time that you went above and beyond to help someone (preferably in a work setting, but a personal interaction is fine)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Why you want to work at ProTrainings&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Your résumé&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Stretch Internet Customer Champion</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/stretch-internet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 9 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/stretch-internet.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are you interested in genuinely helping people on a daily basis? Do you understand what it means to truly deliver a world class customer experience?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At Stretch Internet, our above-all-else focus on supporting our clients defines who we are as a company. We empower our support specialists, daily, to help us establish and deliver on our industry-leading brand of customer service. We’ve been providing streaming services for collegiate athletic departments for more than 12 years and we are the largest streaming provider in the industry, with a client base of more than 500 colleges and universities. We’re looking for team members that can take a new topic, become an expert on it – with training provided, of course – and apply that expertise in a way that truly dazzles (think virtual jazz hands). If you get excited by the prospect of working around sports for a living and appreciate the idea of working on a small, but close-knit team, this could be the job for you!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You are:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;An outstanding communicator (both written and spoken) – think 9 or better on a scale of 1 to 10&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Able to quickly and efficiently communicate with coworkers in an often fast-paced environment&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The person in your circle of friends that everybody seeks out when they’re having an issue with technology&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Appreciative of spectacular service and recognize what sets it apart from the average interaction&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Someone who ascribes to our seven key values as outlined above – especially the first two (“Be kind” and “Be positive”)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Able to put anyone at ease through natural, easy-going conversation (If you’re on an airplane for three hours, you can navigate that fine line of friendly conversation vs. endless badgering)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A cool customer - you never get rattled and your friends often wonder if there’s anything that could make you angry&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Self-motivated – when there is downtime, you are not sitting idly by… you would rather find something new to learn or tinker with&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;You have:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;At least 1-2 years of experience in some field involving customer service interaction and/or high-capacity communication&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Willingness to work at least 1-3 nights per week and full shifts on Saturdays (from late August through May) and occasional Sunday shifts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working with Macs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A desire to develop and nurture client relationships&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Openness to being taught &amp;amp;amp; coached – while we encourage our staff to insert their personality (one of our core values is “Be Yourself”), we do have a well-developed voice that we want each of our support specialists to embrace&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Why Stretch?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We think Stretch is a pretty awesome place to work, and we think you might agree. Check out some of the perks we offer:&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Laid back environment - wear shorts and flip flops to the office if that’s your thing&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- We have fun on a daily basis – ping-pong, darts, pool, sports… somehow we still manage to get work done&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Fully stocked kitchen and catered lunches on Saturdays&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Flexible vacation (3 weeks plus option to buy additional vacation in the summer)&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;- Optional benefits include health insurance and retirement account with employee match&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Glow Customer Experience Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/glow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 7 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/glow.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our team manages online support and advocates on behalf of the women who use our apps from period to parenting. We are looking for a rockstar problem- solver with a proactive attitude, excellent communication skills, and of course, tons of enthusiasm for our women&amp;#39;s health products.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a CX Specialist, you would be an expert on the customer experience of two of our products: either Eve and Glow or Nurture and Baby. You&amp;#39;ll reply to every customer email for your products. You&amp;#39;ll know the ins- and- outs of every feature, every bug, and every customer request. You&amp;#39;ll be able to sense whether our customers will like a feature before we launch it. And once a feature is launched, you&amp;#39;ll be the first to report customer sentiment back to Product.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Delightful, efficient handling of a high volume of customer support requests as a primary priority&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ownership of all bug triage, troubleshooting, user feedback consolidation, Help Center maintenance and email template creation for two of our four apps (Eve and Glow or Nurture and Baby)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Enthusiastic teamwork: inter- team and cross- functional teamwork is the foundation of the job.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exceptionally effective cross- functional communication: open, thorough, timely communication with all teams in the company is a must.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Reporting and resolving inefficiencies in product, policy, workflow etc. We’re constantly looking to improve!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Requirements&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;1+ years of experience in support at a tech company (2- 5+ years preferred)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Analytical, critical attention to even the smallest details, ability to seek and retain knowledge, share and apply it in the future&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Strong desire and ability to provide exceptional customer support and advocate on behalf of the customer&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to work independently and effectively under pressure in a fast- paced environment.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working with help ticketing systems, administrative internal tools, forums, etc.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Bonus&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Knowledge and understanding of women’s reproductive health&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Salary and Equity based on experience.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;How to apply&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Email &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:jobs@glowing.com&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:&amp;amp;#106;o&amp;amp;#98;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#x40;&amp;amp;#x67;&amp;amp;#x6c;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#x77;&amp;amp;#x69;n&amp;amp;#103;&amp;amp;#x2e;&amp;amp;#99;o&amp;amp;#109;&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#106;o&amp;amp;#98;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#x40;&amp;amp;#x67;&amp;amp;#x6c;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#x77;&amp;amp;#x69;n&amp;amp;#103;&amp;amp;#x2e;&amp;amp;#99;o&amp;amp;#109;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and mention Support Driven in the subject!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Code Climate Customer Success Manager</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/code-climate.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 6 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/code-climate.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Code Climate is the world&amp;#39;s largest static analysis platform, helping over 50,000 developers improve the health of their codebases. We work hard to provide clear, timely and actionable insights derived from source code. We recently launched the Code Climate Platform, the first open, extensible platform for all types of static analysis.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Code Climate is available on our hosted platform for free for open source projects, and offers paid subscriptions to analyze private source code either on our hosted platform or Code Climate Enterprise, our behind the firewall product. Our customers include Fortune 500s, public and private companies, large and small, with a range of technical sophistication and exposure to static analysis.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Customer Success Manager you’ll work with customers to help them achieve their software goals, primarily (but not necessarily exclusively) using Code Climate. You’ll also work closely with our engineering and customer service teams as a voice for these customers within the company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a key part of the external face of Code Climate, we&amp;#39;re looking for someone who is invested in the success of our customers, and represents our values well by putting customers first and executing rigorously.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Examples of problems you&amp;#39;ll be solving:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Becoming an active and positive collaborator in the customer’s mission to better improve their code and software development processes by learning about their unique goals, successes and challenges.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Navigating organizations to determine who are the influencers and decision makers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Training clients and promoting wider and deeper Code Climate adoption within their organizations.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Educating customers with unique software development processes and environments about the best way to use Code Climate.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Concierge onboarding for customers with large teams of developers to ensure smooth integration of Code Climate into their organization&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Integrating Code Climate into an organization’s existing IT environment -- including source code management, code review tools, and collaboration tools like Trello and Slack.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Diagnosing issues affecting customers and collaborating with the product engineering team to identify solutions (and creatively suggesting workarounds, when necessary).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;re awesome because:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You elicit glowing testimonials from customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You communicate clearly, concisely and honestly. Customers trust you.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You empathize with issues customers face and are compelled to solve them.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You continually advocate internally on behalf of customers, and can name from memory the problems that our biggest customers face.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;re never afraid to strike up a conversation with someone new, online or in person.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re comfortable having discussions with both technical and non-technical stakeholders.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;re able to navigate complex organizations.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;re technologically curious and always learning.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Working at Code Climate&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Join a small team of around fifteen full-time people who love what they do.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Competitive compensation and meaningful stock options.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flexible and generous paid time off including an open vacation policy and maternity/paternity leave.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Health, dental and vision insurance. We pay 100% of the premium and 50% of the premium for dependents.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Company retreats twice a year. So far we&amp;#39;ve gone to Bali and San Diego.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Opportunities to continue your professional development, including attending tech conferences.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Dog-friendly office stocked with snacks, drinks and cold-brew iced coffee.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>ActiveCampaign Platform Specialist - Australia</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/activecampaign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 3 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/activecampaign.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ActiveCampaign is a platform focused on email, marketing automation, and sales for small businesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;WHAT YOUR DAY COULD CONSIST OF:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Assisting users via email, live chat, and phone&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Consulting with clients to help them utilize our platform to achieve their unique goals&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Conducting live demos of our platform with screensharing.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Keeping on top of the latest news in regards to email marketing, deliverability, and small business marketing in general.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;WHAT IS NEEDED:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Past experience with sales and customer service — specifically with SAAS solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Past experience with email marketing, marketing automation, and/or marketing in general&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The ability to efficiently respond to a significant number of emails, chats, &amp;amp;amp; phone calls per day (once you are up to speed you should be handling over 100 requests a day)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A self-motivated and driven attitude where you will work towards achieving new goals&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent communication skills &amp;amp;amp; the ability to relate to others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Input matters, your work has a high impact, and everyone is working together.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being able to take a general idea and add your own insight and tweaks to it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Spreedly Technical Customer Support Manager (remote)</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/spreedly.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 3 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/spreedly.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Spreedly is a fast-growing startup that is building out a support team to keep up with our expanding customer growth. We need an experienced technical support person that can jump into the role, start learning, and contribute quickly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;#39;re a payments API that’s used by developers around the world. This makes the technical aspect of a support team member very important, so we are looking for someone who can code. Today our engineering team primarily works with Ruby, Rails, Riak, Postgres, Redis, and Linux; tomorrow could see them using Elixir, Rust, Kafka, FreeBSD, etc. We need someone with grit enough to dive into code to troubleshoot customer problems, but who can also express empathy and patience in moments of confusion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’ll be spending the majority of your time answering customer inquiries and researching issues, as well as consistently updating and maintaining documentation and other customer-facing materials to make our customers’ experience with Spreedly as simple as possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with customers and find resolutions to their questions as quickly and simply as possible.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Speak to customers daily with an engaging personality, polished written/verbal communication skills, and meticulous attention to detail.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Support Spreedly’s self-service goals by guiding prospects and customers to use the rich, publicly available resources to best serve their initial and ongoing use of the service.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Discover and analyze gaps in customer experience and identify early warning signals that lead to churn - and then work with other teams to address root causes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Build compelling business cases backed by data to introduce new processes or functions that will drive customer success at scale.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;QUALIFICATIONS&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proven experience working with technical customers/end users, who are primarily developers using our API to support commerce businesses, including heavy usage of curl, Git, etc.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The confidence and ability to embrace new technologies, as needed, to advance Spreedly’s ever changing support goals.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to operate semi-autonomously to incorporate your own immediate priorities with the longer-term and ever-shifting needs of a startup environment.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Consultative and investigative mindset with the ability to find the right pieces of information to put together the whole puzzle.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Demonstrated ability to work remotely with desire to work Pacific time zone hours; i.e. UTC-7.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Our team is largely based in the RDU area of North Carolina, however we are looking for someone remote for this opportunity who will ideally be located on the West coast of the U.S.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The team needs people that are great at their job who know how to elevate the team members and customers around them. You must enjoy talking to customers every day, but always be looking for new ways to automate yourself out of the job. Your contributions will be formative in helping to build the support org from the ground up. This opportunity is perfect for someone with an unmatched passion for understanding customers’ needs and connecting the dots to make them continuously successful with our service.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Envoy Customer Ambassador</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/envoy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 2 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/envoy.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;ABOUT US:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Envoy&amp;#39;s mission is to have awesome visitor and employee experiences become universal in the workplace. With our first product – Envoy Visitor Registration – we’re reimagining the future of the front desk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Envoy is an all-in-one visitor management solution. From collecting visitor information and signatures to host notification, visitor pre-registration, and more. Thousands of companies rely on Envoy to elegantly welcome visitors and keep their information safe and secure. Our focus on good design and customer service set us apart from the myriad other enterprise software companies that settle for &amp;#39;good enough.&amp;#39;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Envoy is backed by Andreessen Horowitz and has served over 4M visitors in 55 countries since it was founded in 2013. Envoy is used by some of today’s most exciting brands including Box, Pinterest, Pixar, GoPro and Mailchimp.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;ABOUT YOU:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’re self-motivated, love making people happy, and have a talent for resolving customer issues with a smile. As an Envoy Customer Ambassador, you’ll be responsible for creating amazing customer experiences, helping us improve our team workflow, and putting out the occasional fire.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Qualify, prioritize, and close customer issues.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Monitor and address customer tickets and Live Chats.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with the team to identify, report, and resolve issues and file bug reports.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work with customers to trouble-shoot technical problems, ranging from integrations to hardware.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understand common customer issues to better inform support processes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Champion the customer&amp;#39;s issues and feature requests with the product team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Help refine the processes for the Envoy Ambassadors team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;MUST HAVES:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience working with customers, either in a call center or retail position.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Desire to go above and beyond to help customers achieve the best experience.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Passion for problem solving and the right attitude and aptitude for learning new technology.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent written and verbal skills; ability to explain the complex in a simple manner.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Love talking to people, and desire to help people through tough issues.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Expensify UK Success Coach</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/expensify-coach.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 2 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/expensify-coach.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Your Mission, Should You Choose to Accept:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Expensify prides itself on solving real-world problems with a team of top-notch product experts. We are reinventing the way people look at expense reports by automating not just the expense report, but the entire business trip. Joining our team means you are helping us fight the good fight against expense reports that suck!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About The Job&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Success Coach, you will be focused on making sure that our customers are successful in using Expensify to solve the problems they face. You’ll do this by applying a deep understanding of our customers, their processes, our product and the systems with which we integrate. You’ll also gather feedback on how we can evolve Expensify to meet our customer’s needs in the future, and apply your product knowledge to map out these improvements for engineering. When product changes happen, you’ll lead the charge via documentation, blog posts, emails, calls and in-person visits with our customers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Joining our team means you will be working in our fast-paced environment and you are fearless of our next big challenge. Even though we work hard at Expensify, we make sure our employees are happy. Our most-discussed perk is our offshore, where we spend a month abroad working as a team from a remote location. Last year we went to Cambodia and Thailand. Where do you want to go next?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About You&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’re an entrepreneur who enjoys thinking through challenging problems, working across functional groups and articulating yourself in both technical and non-technical settings. You’re poised and confident when talking to customers and can always find the time to work with your colleagues to get any issue resolved.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the best possible fit, we are looking for someone who:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Has excellent communication skills. One moment you may be having a technical discussion with an engineer about the product implications of a new feature, the next moment need to communicate how we are going to sell this feature with a member of the sales team, before quickly moving on to working directly with a non-technical customer to fix a problem. The ideal candidate will be able to clearly articulate themselves in all scenarios.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Is passionate about building, maintaining and making our software better. It’s what we do as a company.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can manage time and prioritize efficiently. Things move quickly in this environment and it’s crucial that you are able to react to new information and re-prioritize accordingly.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Is comfortable learning from peers in an informal fashion. After all, we&amp;#39;re all learning things as we go. We also love anyone who&amp;#39;s able to effectively train colleagues as we grow the team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Is well-versed in saying “no”. We often have to say no to ensure that our product stays simple and user-friendly. Saying no and having a compelling argument as to why requires in-depth product knowledge and knowledge of the problem that the customer is trying to solve and is critical to success in this role.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Next Steps&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like what you see? Applying is easy, but it takes time. See, while we know you&amp;#39;re awesome, it&amp;#39;s actually really hard and time consuming to find you in the midst of literally hundreds of other applications we get from everyone else. So this is where we&amp;#39;re going to ask our first favor: can you make it really easy and obvious how great you are, so we don&amp;#39;t accidentally overlook you? There are probably many ways to do that, but the easiest way is to help us out by answering the following questions:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Describe a memorable experience - whether at work or in your personal life - working with a client/customer. What issue did they face, and and how you were able to address their concerns? If you weren&amp;#39;t successful addressing their concerns, why not?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you were tasked with analyzing customer behavior and recommending product-driven solutions, how would you approach that problem?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Describe a scenario where you interacted with an irate person. How were you able to turn them around (assuming you were able to)?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What do you want to do with your life, and how is Expensify a step toward those long-term goals?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How did you hear about us? A job posting? Chalk on a sidewalk? From a friend? Let us know where you saw this opening.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Expensify UK Customer Success</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/expensify.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 2 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/expensify.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Your Mission, Should You Choose to Accept:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Expensify prides itself in solving a real world problem with a team of top notch product experts. We are reinventing the way people look at expense reports by automating not just the expense report, but the entire business trip. Joining our team means you are helping us fight the good fight against expense reports that suck!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are expanding into the UK market and it&amp;#39;s very early stage for our London based team. Help shape the team that will launch our global domination of expense reports and maintain a standard of excellence around the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About The Job&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a member of the Customer Success Team, you will be focused on making our user base successful Expensify users, through a deep understanding of our product and its many applications.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Joining our team means you will be working in our fast paced environment and you are fearless of our next big challenge. Even though we work hard at Expensify, we make sure our employees are happy. Our most discussed perk is our offshore where we spend a month abroad working from a remote location as a team. This year we went to Cambodia and Thailand. Where do you want to go next?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About You&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’re an entrepreneurial extrovert who loves developing relationships with others and helping them solve complex problems with the ease of a trapeze artist! You’ll be talking to users through email, chat, and when needed on the phone, assisting with the onboarding process for potential customers, and working with with existing customers to make sure they are getting the most out of Expensify. The sky’s the limit for you, and this position can also be a jumping off point into other teams within the organization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the best possible fit, we are looking for someone who:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can communicate to all levels within a company in a professional manner&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Is a team player with great interpersonal skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Wants to contribute to the growth of this team for the future&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can provide excellent verbal and written communication with clients&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bonus: Some general understanding of the accounting process, Not required!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Next Steps&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like what you see? Applying is easy, but it takes time. See, while we know you&amp;#39;re awesome, it&amp;#39;s actually really hard and time consuming to find you in the midst of literally hundreds of other applications we get from everyone else. So this is where we&amp;#39;re going to ask our first favor: can you make it really easy and obvious how great you are, so we don&amp;#39;t accidentally overlook you? There are probably many ways to do that, but the easiest way is to help us out by answering the following questions:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What was your first customer support position? What did you support, and what was your personal take on the product and how best to support it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you were given free reign to choose the optimal set of customer support tools, what would they be and how would they optimize your customer success approach? (Feel free to list actual sales tools you’ve used, or fictitious ones. You’ve got free reign).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Describe the angriest customer you have had to support, and how were you able to turn them around? (Assuming you were able to!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pretend you had a month to do whatever you wanted. What would you do? And would this be sufficient time to accomplish the goals you set out to achieve?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What do you want to do with your life, and how is Expensify a step toward those long-term goals?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How did you hear about us? A job posting? Chalk on a sidewalk? From a friend? Let us know where you saw this opening.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Insightly Customer Service Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/insightly.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 2 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/insightly.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insightly is looking for a Customer Service Specialist in San Francisco who not only loves to help customers, but also genuinely cares about them. If you’re a team player who wants to help us continue to grow Insightly, we’d love to talk to you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insightly is dedicated to giving our customers fast, helpful, and friendly answers to any questions they have about our application. In this role, you’ll answer how-to questions, as well as questions about Insightly functionality and integrations. We have some of the most passionate customers worldwide, so sharing their feedback to influence where we take Insightly is a critical part of this role.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reports to: Senior Customer Service Manager&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hours: Full time&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;When you apply (required), tell us briefly:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Why do you want to be part of the Insightly team?&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Why are you the best candidate for this role?&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;What’s the best part of working in customer support?&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Responsibilities&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Become an Insightly product and features expert.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Help customers get the most out of our software and respond to customer requests via email ticket support, support requests that come up in our online community, and phone requests.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Escalate support requests and bugs to engineering team - triage, diagnose, and resolve technical issues and reduce support requests.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Develop and maintain relationships with QA and engineering teams for swift resolution of bugs, service interruptions, and other service-related issues.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Solve tickets using Zendesk, and help the team to get the most out of it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Listen to customers’ needs effectively and share feedback with the engineering team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Provide input to the Insightly Product team on feature improvements and customers’ business challenges.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be a self-starter - identify and implement efficiencies and best practices. Identify trends/issues and come up with solutions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Required Skills&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hands-on experience with cloud-based solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with CRM a plus&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience providing B2B a plus&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent written and communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to troubleshoot&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Curiosity, and a passion for learning&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with Google Apps for Business&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Basic computer skills including Microsoft Windows environment, Google Apps, and familiarity with various browsers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must embody a great deal of patience&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be a customer service star with a technical background and troubleshooting skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with a ticket-based support tool (like Zendesk) and phone-based support&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Must possess a great deal of customer empathy and have a good understanding of how to provide a great experience for customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Comfortable with learning new technologies and solutions and answering customer concerns via phone, email and online communities&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A passion for small business, CRM, and start-ups&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Metrics-driven - can move quickly through tickets, yet maintain a high level of customer satisfaction&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About this company&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over a million users in 150 countries rely on Insightly’s intuitive cloud-based CRM project management solution to track customer interactions and manage contacts, proposals, opportunities, projects and files every day. Insightly’s service integrates seamlessly with Gmail and Outlook, and it has consistently ranked as the No. 1 CRM application on the Google Apps Marketplace. Insightly recently concluded a Series C financing round and is backed by Emergence Capital Partners, Cloud Apps Management LC, Sozo ventures, and TrueBridge Capital Partners. We are based in San Francisco and conveniently located close to Muni, Bart, and Caltrain. We provide competitive compensation packages, stock options, full medical and other benefits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Company Perks&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We’re not only a super successful and fast growing start-up, but also a fun place to work. Here are just some of the perks we offer:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Awesome office in SOMA, San Francisco, close to Caltrain, BART and Muni&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Transportation: Clipper card&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Lunch and Happy Hour Fridays&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flexible working arrangements&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Generous medical, vision, and dental coverage&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Free snacks, drinks, and fruit&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Weekly massages from professional masseurs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>7Geese Customer Support Manager</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/7geese.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/7geese.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7Geese is seeking an energetic and talented Customer Support Manager with a passion for helping customers and a relentless desire to improve customer support best practices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In this role, you will own customer support interactions, resources, processes, and strategy. You will work very closely with the Customer Success and Product Development teams to collaborate on support resources and engagement projects.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At 7Geese, customer support means delighting customers with positive and memorable experiences that provide outcome-based solutions. We believe that finding and seeking help shouldn&amp;#39;t be a chore. Do you agree?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Start Date: ASAP&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Our guide to hiring rockstar support teammates:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You invite scrutiny and exude positivity. Not every interaction is going to involve a ‘yes’, but you believe you can still delight and offer help. Honesty and empathy are your biggest soft-skills.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You avoid negativity and have integrity. You believe feedback of all kinds can lead to improvement. There are insightful opportunities in every interaction.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are proactive and love teaching others. Simply being responsive and giving one-time solutions doesn’t meet 7Geese standards. You value helping others become self-sufficient and enjoy creating structures and resources for learning.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;HERE AT 7GEESE, SUPPORT MEANS YOU...&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Are a rockstar prioritizer and can communicate priorities to the many people who will need you to help them.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have a natural ability to adapt your tone and expressions to those who you’re helping.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Can express complex ideas simply and elegantly. Are not intimidated by technology or terminology.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Thrive off learning new things. You want to continuously progress in your role and take on more responsibility.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have the ability to communicate across multiple time zones and cultures. (Don’t worry, you won’t have to work at 1am).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Are comfortable with debugging and quality testing. You won’t be coding, but you’re comfortable talking to developers and using products like Github to stay informed with what’s going on with product development.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Are excited to work with other 7Geese team members to implement process improvements, resources, and develop kick-ass support practices.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;BREAKDOWN OF HOW YOUR TIME WILL BE SPENT:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;50% Reactive support via Intercom (incoming support questions, e-mails, phone calls, and potential visits). You know the product inside and out; other teams come to fact-check things with you like &amp;quot;Can a person with this permission do this?&amp;quot;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;25% Writing and maintaining content for our learning center and knowledge base. If there&amp;#39;s nothing new to update, you&amp;#39;re researching new best practices and creating new resources to add.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;10% Bug tracking and quality testing. As things get reported, you stay in the know and act as liaison between product development and the customer.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;10% Pro-active engagement (re-engagement emails, developing engagement campaigns to help champion our customers through ideal customer journeys).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;5% Reporting for monthly and quarterly meetings. Tracking KPIs, suggesting other metrics to track based on our goals, summarizing things like top 3 reasons for tickets in a given time period with suggested solutions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;YOUR EXPERIENCE!&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have a minimum of 1 year customer support experience, preferably in a SaaS / startup environment&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have demonstrated superhero like qualities in your current situation and are ready to soar into a new opportunity and take ownership of Customer Support at 7Geese&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have experience working in teams and are confident collaborating with others&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have exhibited our 3 core value areas: excellence, positivity, and growth&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Are communication driven with experience explaining complex problems in easy ways&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have experience delivering solutions to others that help them move forward&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bonus: ability to do product screencasts, basic photo/video editing or graphic design to create content for the support center&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>ShopStorm Customer Success Specialist</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/shopstorm.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/shopstorm.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ShopStorm is looking for a Customer Success Specialist to join our fully distributed team. You’ll be responsible for supporting a growing set of Shopify apps which help power thousands of online stores.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Role&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’ll be the primary point of contact for our customers, helping them with problems, and answering questions. As part of a small team, you&amp;#39;ll likely get your hands dirty with a little bit of everything. Here are some things you may do on a given day:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Serve as the key point person for ShopStorm’s customers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Help customers by troubleshooting problems and answering questions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Install and modify code on customers’ Shopify stores&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Author technical documentation and blog posts to help our customers help themselves&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Help our engineering/product leads identify existing pain points and prioritize feature releases&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Implement processes to improve support and customer satisfaction&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Monitor social media channels and online forums for opportunities to enhance our brand&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Assist with marketing and partnership efforts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About You&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You have that unique combination of technical aptitude and empathy for the user. You’re comfortable with code but prefer to be customer-facing. You’re self-driven with a sense of urgency and draw satisfaction from going above and beyond to provide solutions. You’re an excellent communicator and have the ability to thrive in a distributed environment. Perhaps most importantly, you have a willingness to learn.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About Us&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ShopStorm is a small team focused on creating high-quality Shopify apps with exceptional customer service. All types and size of merchants, from the smallest 1-person online shop to large, multinational eCommerce powerhouses rely on our apps to help their businesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our team is part of SkyVerge, an eCommerce software company that builds tools for tens of thousands of merchants across many different platforms. We’re a distributed company with an even gender split that spans 4 US states and 5 countries. We believe in open communication, respect each other’s diversity of thought, and often find that a well-timed GIF or emoji is the best way to communicate. 🐵&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Requirements&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;To succeed in this position you will have:&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Experience with HTML / CSS, knowledge of JavaScript a big plus!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Native-level fluency in English&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fantastic written communication and interpersonal skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;An endless curiosity for our products and our users&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ability to thrive in a remote environment (along with a reliable internet connection)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Availability for 1-2 team trips / year&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with eCommerce or SaaS products&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Bootcamp&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a full-time, salaried position, but hours are flexible. We know your work will speak for itself through delighted customers and well-written documentation and blog posts. However, fit with our team and culture is important.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every new team member completes a 60-day Bootcamp as a contractor before becoming a salaried employee. Already have a full-time position? Don’t worry. We’re flexible with hours and schedule during the bootcamp period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Package&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some of the benefits we&amp;#39;re excited to offer to our team members:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Competitive salary with performance incentives&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;15 days of paid time-off per year&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Generous holiday policy including two company holidays: SkyVerge Day in March, Founders Day in June 😀&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Medical, dental, and vision insurance (reimbursements for comparable care for non-US/Canadian residents)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Retirement plan with company match&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Home office or co-working allowance&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hardware and software allowance (we&amp;#39;ll set you up with the tools you need to be productive)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Personal development allowance to help you learn and grow (e.g. books, courses, conferences)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A Kindle to help you keep learning!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL, DR: Join our team and influence thousands of online stores. Excited? Us too. Apply now!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;SkyVerge believes and supports workplace diversity. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, gender identity or expression, national origin, age, military service eligibility, veteran status, sexual orientation, marital status, physical or mental disability, or any other protected class.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Papertrail Customer Success Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/papertrail.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/papertrail.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://papertrailapp.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Papertrail&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; provides log management as a service. We work with tens of thousands of ops-savvy developers, systems engineers, and entrepreneurs at companies like GitHub, Heroku, Instacart, Adobe, and DNSimple.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;#39;s where you come in. We&amp;#39;ve grown to need technical customer support to help customers make the most of Papertrail. Here&amp;#39;s a few examples of what customers think of Papertrail&amp;#39;s support:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://twitter.com/TiuTalk/status/714592766827872257&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/TiuTalk/status/714592766827872257&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://twitter.com/agmakonts/status/730356796607614976&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/agmakonts/status/730356796607614976&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://twitter.com/hectcastro/status/717523363032391680&amp;quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/hectcastro/status/717523363032391680&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Summary&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Put smiles on the faces of fellow engineers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Remote work is welcome&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;100% online (email, Slack/Campfire text chat), no phones&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Startup atmosphere and tools, public company benefits&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Okay, cool. What&amp;#39;s involved?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Help customers setup and use Papertrail&amp;#39;s service in email and text chat. The questions are about a wide range of topics like Linux, syslog, Web framework logging, Ruby, Rails, IP stack troubleshooting, PHP, REST/JSON, Python, firewall rules, Node.js, plus non-technical topics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You almost certainly won&amp;#39;t know about all of these. While a strong working knowledge of Linux is required, Googling to satisfy your own curiosity is a lot more valuable (and hopefully, fun). Also:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Be comfortable and personable in email, even when interacting with strangers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Show a passion for devops tools, Web services, and technology in general. We&amp;#39;re doing this because we love it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Requirements&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Working Linux knowledge&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. You&amp;#39;ve compiled a binary, installed packages, and understand TCP/IP concepts. Experience with tools like &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;tcpdump&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;strace&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; will help, though it isn&amp;#39;t required.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Fantastic casual writing skills&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. This job involves helping people in email, forums, and text chat, so a written voice goes a long way. Good grammar is critical, as is a gut feel for when to ignore it in order to make a personal connection. When a friend emails you a question, do you spend 10 minutes Googling and send them a ridiculously thoughtful answer? You&amp;#39;ll fit right in. A public online history (like a blog, Stack Overflow/Server Fault posts, GitHub commit history, Twitter account, or casual posts to non-technical online forums) is ideal, since a big part of this job is showing your passion and knowledge for a topic in casual, freeform emails.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Scripting&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Experience in a scripting or programming language, ideally in one or more of Ruby, Python, Go, Java, or C.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Location and timezone&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Able to work in US, Canada, or Europe on a roughly UTC-7 workday. Although we&amp;#39;re completely location-agnostic, employment law is not.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Why is this unusually awesome?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;#39;s the most important thing we do. Happy customers are the only reason why we get to do this every day. Since most of our interactions with customers are via support, this is the most important thing we do every day and the main reason we grow. It&amp;#39;s:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Flexible.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Papertrail&amp;#39;s hub is a Slack text chat channel. Work in a coffee shop without missing office conversation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Personal&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. You&amp;#39;ll be part of a tiny team, working side by side with the founders. Debating product decisions is a lot more fun because we&amp;#39;re all target users – 100% of Papertrail staff has sent a GitHub pull request.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The tip of the iceberg&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Although answering questions is the must-have, you&amp;#39;re welcome to write docs, improve our open-source apps, or grow into coding on the core service. We operate in 3 thriving fields: cloud computing, software as a service, and dev/ops, and the tools we use are in demand: Ruby, Java/Scala, and current open-source libraries.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Predictable&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. As part of SolarWinds, Papertrail offers excellent benefits, including paid health insurance and 401(k) match. If you&amp;#39;re in San Francisco or Austin, you&amp;#39;re welcome to come in to a physical office.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;About Papertrail&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;#39;re part of SolarWinds, which includes &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.librato.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Librato&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.pingdom.com&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Pingdom&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. You can see some of the things we think about on &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://twitter.com/papertrailapp&amp;quot;&amp;gt;@papertrailapp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;SolarWinds (SWI) is on Forbes&amp;#39; lists of &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.forbes.com/growth-companies/list/#tab:rank&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Most Innovative Growth Companies&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.forbes.com/best-small-companies/list/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;America&amp;#39;s Best Small Companies&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Yeomen Community Support Team Lead</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/yeomen.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/yeomen.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Company:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Yeomen are a community of support experts who build and staff customized support solutions for companies and organizations. We specialize in creating help desks that don’t just resolve problems, but also foster brand loyalty and growth by cultivating relationships with user communities. Our mission is to bring a human element to support by connecting customers to real people who care about customer concerns and work hard to resolve their issues with compassion, care, and positivity. More information about The Yeomen can be found at theyeomen.com.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Yeomen is proud to be a support partner for Vimeo, the leading video platform for creative professionals. We are currently looking for an experienced manager to lead the team of 18 Yeomen support ninjas who engage and support the Vimeo community day in and day out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;The Job:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a full time position.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Yeomen is based in the United States. This opening is for someone residing within the US that can telecommute from their current location.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What you’d be doing for support:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Answering tech support and customer service questions by email.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshooting video playback issues.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Supporting account access for all level accounts (Basic, Plus, &amp;amp;amp; PRO)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Helping with billing and purchases.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Walking someone through uploading and downloading a video.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Educating users of privacy settings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Identifying recurring customer issues, helping to solve them, and escalating them to others for review.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Writing customer response templates and online help documentation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Making customers very happy.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Having coffee with us.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What you’d be doing for your team:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Liaising between client contact and support team members.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Coordinating schedules, including shift rotations and time off requests for three separate shifts.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Leading monthly one on one meetings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Developing well-rounded metrics for success and using these to help your team grow professionally.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Creating documentation &amp;amp;amp; reporting of performance metrics.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working with members of the team to set and reach career goals.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>PrecisionLender Client Support Superhero</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/precisionlender.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/precisionlender.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Client Support Superhero, you will support, educate, and empower our clients and end-users so that they can be successful. You will own the client support experience and work to exceed clients&amp;#39; expectations by genuinely caring about them, personally &amp;amp;amp; professionally.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What Your Superpowers Are:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Passionately helping others.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Explaining complex issues in beautifully simple terms.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Listening way more than you talk and connecting with people.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Embracing change &amp;amp;amp; adapting quickly.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Managing multiple projects simultaneously.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A natural ability to see the full scope of a problem, in order to ask the right questions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Never letting a detail fall through the cracks.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Using social media or web-based software, including Twitter, Facebook, Google Apps.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Familiarity with common help-desk/ticketing solutions such as Zendesk and Jira.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;How You Will Use Your Powers:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Saving clients across the country from any issues they are having.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Evaluate, troubleshoot, and follow-up on client issues as well as replicate and document for further escalation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Develop support content including articles, blog posts, videos and other collateral. You may not author all that content, but you will work with our development and consulting teams to identify content needs and get them filled.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being a voice for clients and fighting for their causes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Drive product change and improvement by working with our Product Development team to document changes and improvements to our software and ensure that our Clients are aware of those changes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Foster our community of users to stimulate the sharing of ideas so that we can get our best clients talking to each other and cross-pollinating those ideas.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Your Experience &amp;amp;amp; Education:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You may be fresh out of college or you may have 10 years under your belt - either way, you need to have spent significant time working in a business setting, ideally in areas like customer service, internal and external client support.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;Bachelors Degree preferred&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;How You Should Apply:&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;#39;re looking for people who pay attention and care about their future. If you want to be considered for this position, you have to answer the application questions, this is us testing your attention to detail.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The final step in our hiring process will be for you to arrange personal reference calls with former supervisors as well as others we may choose. If you&amp;#39;re awesome, that part will be easy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Automattic Happiness Engineer</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/automattic.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/automattic.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a Happiness Engineer, helping people is your passion. Maybe you’ve developed your own support philosophy by reading books like Delivering Happiness or Exceptional Service, Exceptional Profit. Perhaps you’re a contributor in an online support community such as the &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums or &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Transforming publishing on the web is no small task. Our goal is to build relationships based on trust which result in happy, passionate, loyal customers and colleagues. We do this through listening to their needs and guiding them to the fullest use of the products we offer. We are looking for people with the right mix of compassion, writing skills, and technical knowledge to get the job done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;In general, a typical day involves:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Helping people use Automattic’s products, including &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, WooCommerce, Jetpack, Gravatar, and more&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshooting, investigating, and creating detailed bug reports&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Crafting and editing helpful support documentation&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Being an active member of a team that provides around the clock support to our users via live chat, forums, and email&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Building a community of support by sharing knowledge and insight amongst team members&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Being a Happiness Engineer requires:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Patience, grace, and a sense of humor&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Excellent writing and communication skills&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Working knowledge of WordPress, HTML, and CSS&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A knack for taking technical language and making it understandable&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A passion for solving tough problems and proposing elegant solutions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happiness Engineers must be fluent and eloquent in written English. If you know additional languages, be sure to tell us!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://wordpress.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;WordPress.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; forums are fantastic places to gain the experience required for this position. If you are already active there, let us know! Send a link to your forum profile and we’ll check it out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Harvest Expert</title>
      <link>http://jobs.supportdriven.com/jobs/harvest.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 May 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">jobs/harvest.html</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Disclaimer: Don&amp;#39;t judge us too quickly! We&amp;#39;ve made some intentional typos in this job post. See our To Apply section for more info.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About Harvest&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Harvest creates well-crafted, useful software to help small businesses work better. Today we’re a group of folks &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.getharvest.com/made-on-earth&amp;quot;&amp;gt;all over the globe&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; serving tens of thousands of awesome companies from over 100 countries. We are a team of humble and talented people who genuinely &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.getharvest.com/blog/2012/05/on-craftsmanship/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;care about our craft&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and demand the highest quality.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;Our customers love Harvest for our great products and legendary support, delivered by our Harvest Experts: wicked-smart human being, empathetic problem-solvers, and patient trouble-shooters.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;About You&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re patient and enjoy solving tough problems. You take pride in explaining and helping others understand problems and solutions.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re an exceptional communicator and you treat people kindly. You can gracefully break down, solve, and explain, even the most complex problems. Listening, talking, and working with people makes you happy.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Your writing skills are flawless. We mean it. You must have a savvy style and a firm grip on grammar.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You can de-escalate a tense situation with ease and grace—working through a tough issue or bug with an upset customer not only doesn’t scare you, it’s a challenge you’re eager to take on.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re a hard worker with a history of getting things done carefully and efficiently. You’re thorough—no detail go unnoticed. You’re self motivated, but also enjoy contributing to a team.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You have the ability to switch gears quickly and readjust your focus appropriately.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You don’t mind doing the same thing from day to day. You’re also comfortable jumping onto a side project when the occasion arises and aren’t scared to tackle the new and unknown.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;#39;re happy to work East Coast US business hours of 9am-5pm, give or take an hour in either direction.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What You&amp;#39;ll Do&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learn the ins and outs of Harvest, Harvest Forecast, and are associated apps and integrations.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Answer 20 to 50 customer emails and 10 to 15 phone calls per day.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Troubleshoot technical issues in Harvest and help developers diagnose bugs.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Host webinars for and answer questions from prospective Harvest customers.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Create lively and creative written and video documentation for Harvests Help Center, and keep this documentation up-to-date.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Participate in product development by sharing customer feedback and your unique perspective as a Harvest Expert.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Treat our customers with sincerity, kindness, and respect, and think of new ways to impress, delight, and surprise them.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;To Apply&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Email us at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:customersupport@getharvest.com&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;mailto:&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#117;s&amp;amp;#116;o&amp;amp;#x6d;&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#117;&amp;amp;#112;p&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;amp;#x72;t&amp;amp;#64;&amp;amp;#x67;&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#104;&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#114;&amp;amp;#118;&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#46;&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#x6d;&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#117;s&amp;amp;#116;o&amp;amp;#x6d;&amp;amp;#101;&amp;amp;#x72;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#117;&amp;amp;#112;p&amp;amp;#x6f;&amp;amp;#x72;t&amp;amp;#64;&amp;amp;#x67;&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#104;&amp;amp;#97;&amp;amp;#114;&amp;amp;#118;&amp;amp;#x65;&amp;amp;#x73;&amp;amp;#116;&amp;amp;#46;&amp;amp;#99;&amp;amp;#111;&amp;amp;#x6d;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; with the subject line &amp;quot;Harvest Expert - _______&amp;quot; (fill in your favorite animal).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tell us a bit about yourself and why you you’d make a great Harvest Expert.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You’re awesome and can work anywhere… why Harvest?&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Whoops! We made a few grammatical mistakes in this job post. Let us know what they are.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Due to the high volume of applications we receive, we won’t be able to respond to everyone. While we appreciate your enthusiasm, there’s no need to send follow up emails—if we think you’re a good fit for the team, we’ll be in touch!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No phone calls, please.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>	  
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
